look all righty hi everybody thanks for
大家好，谢谢大家
joining me on this what time is
现在加入我
announced I'm in I'm in beautiful
宣布我在我的美丽中
beautiful bangalore where it is not 20
美丽的班加罗尔，那里不是20
to 30 ish so uh if you're joining us
到30 ish所以嗯，如果您加入我们
from asia good evening if you're joining
来自亚洲的晚上好，如果您要加入
us from europe a happy you know late in
来自欧洲的我们很高兴您知道
the afternoon sort of a to you and then
下午对你来说，然后
if you're joining us from north america
如果您要从北美加入我们
south america parts of it anyway good
无论如何，南美洲的部分地区还是不错的
morning to you so my name is josh long
早上好，我叫乔希
i'm the developer advocate for the open
我是开放的开发者拥护者
source spring technologies at pivotal
源泉技术至关重要
i'm the author of five books now on
我现在是五本书的作者
spring released in greatest of course on
春天当然是在
building resilient robust cloud scale
建立弹性强大的云规模
applications and micro services with
应用程序和微服务
spring boot spring cloud and cloud
spring boot 春季云和云
foundry and i'm the leader of three
铸造厂，我是三个的领导者
instructional videos by addison wesley
艾迪生·韦斯利的教学视频
the books the latest book is on is by
最新的书是在哪本书
o'reilly with the latest video is by
o'reilly的最新视频是
addison wesley pearson and they're on
艾迪生·韦斯利·皮尔森，他们在
the Safari online marketplace and the
Safari在线市场和
latest one of course is a study on
当然最新的一项是对
building applications with spring boot
使用Spring Boot构建应用程序
and the spring cloud and and cloud
还有春天的云和云
foundry so I'm also contributed to
铸造，所以我也为
several open source spring projects not
几个开源春季项目没有
least of which are of course spring
当然，至少其中一些是春天
boots and Spring novation the open
靴子和春季革新开放
source workflow engine activity in Baden
Baden中的源工作流引擎活动
and you know I'm very grateful to be
而且你知道我很感激
here if you have questions if you lead
如果您有疑问，请在这里
this webinar more confused for your time
这次网络研讨会让您更加困惑
with me then when you came in please
然后和我在一起，当你进来的时候
don't hesitate to reach out i'm at
不要犹豫，伸出援助之手
starbucks man with an X on Twitter or
在Twitter上带有X的星巴克人或
there's my email I am as always at your
有我的电子邮件，我一如既往
service I work at pivotal and we are a
服务我在关键部门工作，我们是一个
small little startup in the valley we
山谷中的小小创业公司
started in april of 2013 i work on the
从2013年4月开始，我从事
spring team this is the same spring team
春季队这是同一支春季队
that you will have known and loads for
您将知道并加载的
the better part of last 15 years and we
过去15年的大部分时间，我们
along with the the leadership on the
以及领导层
apache tomcat project the rabbonim q
apache tomcat project rabbonim q
prime
主要
there are distributed data structure
有分布式数据结构
Redis project and of course last but
Redis项目，当然还有最后一个
certainly not least the cloud foundry
当然，尤其是云铸造厂
open source platform as a service
开源平台即服务
project are dedicated to building a
该项目致力于建设一个
modern platform for modern workloads and
用于现代工作负载的现代平台
we asked ourselves selves what can we do
我们自问自己该怎么办
to really empower the modern developer
真正赋予现代开发人员权力
what we can we do to help them build
我们能做些什么来帮助他们建立
applications that work well in the cloud
在云中运行良好的应用程序
which is of course is where a lot of
当然，这是很多
applications are running today and so
应用程序今天正在运行，所以
part of that mission was of course to
该任务的一部分当然是为了
make sort of the getting started
做些入门
experience with spring as easy as
轻松体验春天
possible to for example our spring that
可能例如我们的春天
I know for such guides and the new
我知道这样的指南和新
website and spring boot itself is a
网站和 spring boot 本身是一个
certainly a very very powerful way to be
当然是非常非常有力的方式
productive very quickly but another
生产很快，但另一个
thing we we wanted to tackle is how do
我们想要解决的是如何做
we empower developers to build
我们授权开发人员进行构建
applications that work well in the cloud
在云中运行良好的应用程序
since this is the new runtime that is
因为这是新的运行时
the new space that's a new destination
成为新目的地的新空间
for production right that's new
新的生产权
production and increasing the
生产和增加
applications you know you know with
您知道的应用程序
spring we we've helped people move away
春天，我们帮助人们搬走了
from large sort of bloated application
来自大量的application肿应用
servers and we've helped them make these
服务器，我们已经帮助他们制作了这些
applications as small as possible and
应用程序越小越好
that and that that Exodus has turned out
那和那出埃及记
to be very very very present because of
因为存在而非常非常非常存在
course now we're seeing applications
当然，现在我们看到了应用程序
being deployed in the cloud as services
作为服务部署在云中
as an example of services a suite of
作为服务示例，
services and we're not you know well I
服务，我们不是您很了解我
don't think I'm telling you guys
不要以为我是在告诉你们
anything new this is not news at all
任何新事物根本不是新闻
right we've seen in last so sort of
对，我们在最后看到的
eight years or so we've seen story after
大约八年后，我们看到了故事
story of the big web giant's making the
网路巨人的故事
move to this new architecture this new
搬到这个新架构这个新
story right so of course lots of
故事对，所以当然很多
different applications have moved from
不同的应用已经从
what we'll call a monolithic application
我们称之为单片应用程序
these are large applications wearing all
这些都是大型应用
the services and all the functionality
服务和所有功能
are co-located in the giant assembly a
在大型装配体中共处一处
giant deployable unit like a
大型可部署部队
do you guys remember a long time ago in
你们还记得很久以前吗
a galaxy far away there was something
一个遥远的星系
called a dot e AR artifact and yeah me
叫做点e AR神器，是的，我
either but that was a it was a way of
要么，但这是一种方法
deploying all your services all your web
在网络上部署所有服务
functionality inside of a single
单一功能
deployable unit and that we've seen
可部署单位，我们已经看到
people move away from their architecture
人们远离建筑
a lot in last 15 years into you know
在过去的15年中很多
different small singly focused services
不同的小型单独服务
so Twitter of course moved from a rails
因此，Twitter当然从轨道上移了下来
monolith and moved to a picture that is
巨石并移动到的图片是
more less in microsomes architecture
在微粒体架构中更少
Facebook really had they had a lot
Facebook真的有很多
further to go because of course Twitter
当然会因为Twitter而走得更远
reasonably insanely decided to switch to
合理疯狂地决定改用
the JVM instead of trying to repurpose
JVM，而不是试图改变用途
rails to be the platform that I needed
成为我需要的平台
facebook under the end where I guess
我猜到底在facebook下
they were keen on doubling down on their
他们热衷于加倍
mistakes so they took PHP and we created
错误，所以他们选择了PHP，我们创建了
it so that they could build this
以便他们可以建立这个
platform with a runtime that kind of
运行时这样的平台
looks like the JVM Netflix of course
当然看起来像JVM Netflix
moved from a giant monolithic
从巨型独石搬到
application to a suite of microservices
应用到一套微服务
a ebay linkedin Amazon Google all of
一个ebaylinkedin亚马逊Google全部
these companies some a lot longer ago
这些公司要早得多
than others have had to make this jump
比其他人不得不跳
right and that's not to say that there
是的，那并不是说那里
isn't value in this monolithic
在这个整体中没有价值
application obviously if you've got an
显然，如果您有一个应用程序
application to start today you're not
从今天开始申请
going to leap to divide it into a
打算将其分为
thousand different small pieces you're
成千上万种不同的小物件
going to build the small thing that
将要建造的小东西
could possibly work and as soon as the
可能会工作，并且尽快
restrictions break it up a lot of people
限制使很多人分手
are moving to this sort of architecture
正在转向这种架构
right and there's a lot of different
对，有很多不同
reasons I think some of them are fairly
我认为其中一些是相当合理的原因
obvious so Moore's law of course is this
很明显，所以摩尔定律当然是这样的
idea that computational capacity will
计算能力将
effectively double every 18 months to
每18个月有效地增加一倍，
two years that hasn't been true in more
两年以来，情况并非如此
than a decade but we still think about
超过十年，但我们仍在思考
it as sort of an interesting trend line
作为一种有趣的趋势线
right and of course in order to build
正确的，当然是为了建立
applications that scale today we talk
我们今天讨论规模可扩展的应用程序
about process style concurrency or
关于流程样式并发或
concurrency but especially process al
并发，但尤其是流程
concurrency this idea that I want to run
并发我想运行的想法
more services not one big one that's
更多的服务不是一个大的
that goes up
那上升
we've seen this drive for capacity from
我们已经看到此驱动器从
mobile platform so of course this number
移动平台，所以当然这个数字
is a very old number from 2012 it it's
是2012年以来的非常老的数字
the idea that we have 1.5 million new
我们有150万个新的想法
android activations every day and of
每天都有android激活
course iphone which isn't nearly so fast
当然iPhone不是那么快
growing is also growing very quickly and
增长也非常快，
there's a lot of activations there so
那里有很多激活
we're seeing a lot of new users and a
我们看到了很多新用户，
lot of new people connecting and using
很多新的人连接和使用
apps and making requests for the first
应用程式，并提出要求
time you know every day right and this
你每天都知道的时间
number will continue for a while and
该号码将持续一段时间，并且
even once it can even once it's a sort
即使是一次也可以
of leveled off we'll still have this
的水平，我们仍然有这个
crazy title deluge of mobile driven sort
移动驱动类疯狂标题泛滥
of users we have the social world right
用户拥有我们的社交世界权利
this idea that the applications build on
应用程序建立在这个想法上
top of social networks or social put
社交网络或社交投放的顶部
service providers for example Facebook
服务提供商，例如Facebook
and Twitter and so on every 60 seconds
和Twitter等，每60秒
these services and this is by the way at
这些服务，顺便说一下
a graph from 2012 I think so every 60
我认为2012年的图表
seconds you'll see this crazy amount of
几秒钟，您将看到如此疯狂的数量
activity on these different platforms
在这些不同平台上的活动
and that activity is something that you
那活动就是你
dear developer can can harvest can
亲爱的开发商可以收获
leverage can build upon we see it all
可以依靠我们看到的一切
the time things like Instagram which
像Instagram这样的时间
often have no redeeming value it's over
通常没有赎回价值
to the to the world or humanity at large
走向世界或整个人类
went crazy big entirely on the on the
完全疯了
backs of something like Facebook right
像Facebook这样的东西的背面
we've also seen that things like
我们还看到诸如
farmville you know which is a game that
Farmville，你知道这是一个游戏
get went viral because of its
因为它而流行
integrations with these platforms can go
与这些平台的集成可以进行
huge quickly right so again if you're
快速巨大，如果您是
building applications and you're
构建应用程序，您正在
building on top of these platforms
建立在这些平台之上
there's no reason your app couldn't also
没有理由您的应用也无法
go viral quickly and all this to say
快速传播病毒，所有这些都可以说
that scale is everybody's problem right
规模是每个人的问题吧
it's not just the big webs increasingly
不仅仅是越来越多的大网络
although it's not as much now but it's
虽然现在不多了，但是
certainly becoming very very very
当然变得非常非常非常
political problem we're seeing this this
政治问题，我们看到了这个
move to the Internet of Things this idea
转移到物联网这个想法
that every device has an IP
每个设备都有一个IP
for the three billion or so connected
为三十亿左右的人
human beings on the earth at the moment
此刻人类在地球上
we we say that there are about 25
我们说大约有25
billion devices this is a the number
十亿个设备这是一个数字
from Cisco which is pretty darn
来自思科，这真是太糟糕了
incredible right that's almost 8 devices
令人难以置信的权利，这几乎是8台设备
per for human basically in their sphere
基本上是针对人类的
of influence in their in their lives you
在他们一生中的影响力
know and i can i can easily think about
知道，我可以轻松考虑
my 8 devices you know it's not hard
我知道的8台设备并不难
people there are cars now that have IP
人们现在有拥有IP的汽车
so again this is a this is becoming more
所以这又是一个越来越多的
of a thing you know we're seeing this
你知道我们正在看到的东西
this demand in traffic and if your
这种交通需求，如果您
application isn't prepared for it you're
您尚未准备好应用程序
probably going to lose out we're also
可能会输掉，我们也
seeing organizational impetus for this
看到为此的组织动力
drive right Conway's laws idea that
正确驾驶康威的法律理念
systems are constrained to produce
系统受限于生产
designs which are copies of the
外观设计的副本
communication structures of these
这些的沟通结构
organizations the I've heard it
我听说过的组织
alternatively said as a team that a
或者作为一个团队说
company that or an organization that has
具有的公司或组织
a has fordham teams were kind of
一个福特汉姆队是
compiler will in electively build a four
编译器将选择性地构建一个四
pass compiler you think about Amazon you
通过编译器，您会想到亚马逊吗
think about Netflix these are not one
想想Netflix这些不是一个
application these are in fact several
应用这些实际上是几个
different services inside of one web UI
一个Web UI内的不同服务
right and if you think about those
是的，如果您考虑这些
different services they all have
他们都有不同的服务
different growth rates different
不同的增长率不同
trajectories different business motives
轨迹不同的商业动机
indeed different oftentimes business
确实是经常不同的业务
drivers right they may have different
司机说他们可能有不同
teams different people that care about
团队关心的不同人
their investment in that particular
他们在那方面的投资
feature that particular service amazon
具有特定服务亚马逊的功能
this distinction is far more clear you
这种区别要清楚得多
go to the website you can do a on the
去网站，你可以做一个
search bar there you can click the drop
搜索栏在那里，您可以单击下拉菜单
down you'll see any number of different
下来，您会看到许多不同的
markets and sort of experiences that
市场和那种经历
they expose to people so organizations
他们向人们公开，所以组织
are now being increasingly divided up
现在正在越来越分裂
into small business verticals these
进入小型垂直行业
verticals increasingly have a
垂直行业越来越有
commingling of business leadership and
业务领导力与
technology and operations and so on as
技术和运营等
opposed to you know the tech people over
反对你认识技术人员
there and then business people over here
然后那里的商人
and they the tech people throw a coat of
他们向技术人员扔了一件外套
the wall to operations for example it's
操作的墙，例如
not
不
it's not like that as much anymore so
现在不是那样了
we're seeing a lot of different reasons
我们看到许多不同的原因
for this embrace of this architecture
对于这种架构的拥抱
and this idea of a cloud native
和这种云原生的想法
application and of course when we talk
应用，当然，当我们交谈时
about that Netflix famously described
关于Netflix著名的描述
the cloud native application as being a
云原生应用程序
functional decomposition in terms of
功能分解
microservices this idea that might API
微服务这个可能使用API​​的想法
as my services themselves are going to
因为我自己的服务将
be broken out into process concurrent
分解为并发处理
friendly a api's and no sequel right
友好的api，没有续集权
this idea that my data can be charted
我的数据可以绘制图表的想法
and scaled horizontally as well right so
并水平缩放
this is part of a larger trend today
这是今天更大趋势的一部分
we're going to talk about microservices
我们将谈论微服务
when we talk about microservices there
当我们在那里谈论微服务时
are some rules you may follow one is
您可能会遵循的一些规则是
that you should embrace api's amazon
你应该拥抱api的亚马逊
famously decreed that all their services
著名的法令是，他们所有的服务
should communicate the API that is no
应该传达不存在的API
service shall talk to another services a
服务应与另一服务对话
database state and as a result they had
数据库状态，因此他们有
to do a lot of work to make sure that
做很多工作以确保
their applications are available and
他们的应用程序可用
working and that their applications are
工作，他们的应用程序是
accessible and that it's cheap and
容易获得，而且价格便宜，
friction free to stand these services up
无摩擦地支撑这些服务
another important feature is this idea
另一个重要特征是这个想法
of independent deployability this idea
独立可部署性的想法
that I can deploy a service without
我可以部署服务而无需
synchronizing or waiting on another team
同步或等待另一个团队
we're just as much as possible right
我们尽可能地正确
when we talk about in the independent of
当我们谈论独立于
deployability despite what some perhaps
可部署性，尽管可能有些
miss misguided bloggers may say we're
想念被误导的博客作者可能会说我们
not talking about dll's okay so just
不谈论DLL的问题，所以
just put that one to bed okay so first
刚把那个放到床上好吧，所以先
things first you want to be able to
首先要想做的事
build applications and API is as quickly
建立应用程序和API的速度很快
as possible that should be fairly easy
尽可能简单
if you've had a chance to look at spring
如果你有机会看看春天
boot then you know that it's a dead
启动，那么你知道这已经死了
simple these days to build an API so I'm
这些天来构建API很简单，所以我
going to go ahead and build a little API
继续构建一个小API
here I'll say hello
在这里我打个招呼
hello at gu v okay i'll say at risk
你好，我会说危险的
controller like so class reading rest
像这样的控制器阅读休息
controller okay and i'll say at path
控制器好，我会在路径上说
variable and i'm going to what i'm doing
变量，我要去做什么
here is i'm defining a very simple rest
这是我在定义一个非常简单的休息
api it's a it's just a service or return
api这是一个服务或回报
a sort of a useless message but what I'm
一种无用的信息，但我是
trying to establish here is that if your
试图在这里建立的是，如果您
goal is to get something up and running
目标是启动并运行某些东西
in and you're scared of having to make
进入，您不必担心
everything rest that that friction is
一切都在于那摩擦是
long since disappeared it doesn't cost
很久以来消失不花钱
anything these days to get a service up
这些天来提供服务的一切
and running not even on the JVM so this
甚至不在JVM上运行，所以这
is actually a goofy language script I'm
实际上是我的愚蠢语言脚本
also going to add i'm going to use great
也将添加我将使用很棒
grab which is a groovy language as a
抓住这是一种令人讨厌的语言
call you know it's a facility that's
告诉你，这是一个设施
sort of like maven or Gradle it'll do
有点像行家或Gradle
dependency resolution and bring them
依赖解决方案，并带来他们
into the classpath so i can say i want
进入classpath，所以我可以说我想要
to use the dependency that is have an
使用具有
artifact that is unambiguously
明确的神器
resolvable as spring boot starter
可作为Spring Boot启动器解决
actuator okay and spring run hello to V
执行器正常，弹簧向V打个招呼
and once that starts up it will be
一旦启动，它将是
available localhost reservation so it's
可用的本地主机保留，因此
high
高
we said hello
我们打招呼
poor old ah okay so there we go there's
可怜的老啊，好的，所以我们去那里了
my little rest service up and running
我的小憩服务开始运作
and and that's kind of it right and
就是这样，
actually I can go to for such metrics
其实我可以去做这样的指标
this is by way of the actuator let me
这是通过执行器让我
switch my browser here give you a
在这里切换我的浏览器给你一个
simpler pretty printing plug in here
简单的漂亮打印插件在这里
metrics by I go to metrics and I can get
指标，我可以找到指标
information about the state of the
有关状态的信息
application i go to trace and i can see
我去追踪的应用程序，我可以看到
the request log you know how many
请求日志你知道多少
requests have been made into the
已将请求发送到
application there the headers and so on
应用程序有标题等等
if i go to env i get information about
如果我去env，我会得到有关的信息
the system properties and the java
系统属性和Java
kayvyun properties if i go to dump i get
kayvyun属性，如果我去转储我得到
a stack trace if i go to beans i get in
堆栈跟踪（如果我要进入豆子）
a numeration of all the javabeans as
所有javabeans的计数为
well as their dependencies I go to
以及我去的依赖
mappings I get all the spring MVC
映射我得到了所有的春季MVC
endpoints have been exposed their spring
端点已经暴露在春天
MVC controllers and so on so again it's
MVC控制器，依此类推，再次
very easy to get applications that you
非常容易获得您所需要的应用程序
can monitor you can to analyze and so on
可以监控您可以进行分析等等
in production I can alternatively run
在生产中，我可以选择运行
these as jars so i can say hot you know
这些作为罐子，所以我可以说很热你知道
hideout hideout jar and i'll get a jar
藏身处藏身罐，我去拿个罐子
now and then the same thing as I've just
时不时地和我刚才一样
had before i can say double- jar hi that
在我可以说双罐子之前
jar that'll start up and here we are
将启动的jar，我们在这里
localhost hi there we go and even better
本地主机嗨，我们去，甚至更好
I can alter things very simply with the
我可以用
judicious use of properties right so for
明智地使用财产对
example if you know about spring booth
如果您知道春季展台的示例
then you know it supports a property
那么你知道它支持一个属性
called server that port so i can say
叫服务器那个端口，所以我可以说
java my SD server that port equals eight
java我的SD服务器端口等于八
thousand for example and minus r r
例如千，负rr
equals demo demo or hide out jar and
等于演示演示或隐藏jar和
then start it up and that override the
然后启动它，并覆盖
default and build properties so there we
默认并建立属性，所以我们
are again a thousand right so again it's
又是一千对，所以再次
very very natural to build services very
非常非常自然地建立服务
very quickly if anybody tells you
如果有人告诉你很快
otherwise you can tell them to check out
否则你可以告诉他们退房
spring boot so that isn't the problem
spring boot ，所以这不是问题
right there's no reason you should have
对，没有理由你应该有
any pain building a service today indeed
今天确实很难建立服务
the problem most people faces when they
大多数人在他们遇到的问题
try and get these services to play well
尝试使这些服务正常运行
together that introduces fragility that
一起引入了脆弱性
is where the friction is and it is
是摩擦力所在的地方
because of this that we really really
因此，我们真的
wanted to sort of take spring
想有点春天
further how do we build upon that
进一步，我们如何在此基础上
programming model and address the
编程模型并解决
problem space of service resilience
服务弹性的问题空间
again the example that netflix has is
同样，netflix的示例是
that they've got 600 different
他们有600种不同的
microservices each of which communicates
各自通信的微服务
it you know each of which communicates
你知道每个人都可以交流
with any number of other services and
以及任何其他服务，以及
they're trying to keep their services
他们试图保持他们的服务
and their availabilities as high as
以及它们的可用性高达
possible given six hundred different
可能有六百种不同
microservices it's a little bit naive to
微服务有点天真
assume that they can keep an SLA you
假设他们可以保留您的SLA
know even despite all the right so
即使没事也知道
instead they plan for software that is
相反，他们计划的软件是
resilient to failure and Netflix is not
对失败具有弹性，而Netflix则没有
the only one to have walked this path of
唯一走过这条路的人
course Google of course had to tread
当然，谷歌当然不得不
this path for the beginning Facebook
Facebook的开始之路
famously of course they had to to try
当然，他们必须尝试
and make this work as well Twitter I had
并使这项工作以及我拥有的Twitter
to go this route of course taobao which
走这条路线当然淘宝哪个
is a ecommerce engine in China sort of
是中国的电子商务引擎
like Amazon and eBay accept that taobao
像亚马逊和eBay一样接受淘宝
makes more money than amazon and ebay
比亚马逊和易趣赚更多的钱
combined by a lot and Baidu which is a
与百度相结合，这是一个
search engine that serves 700 to 800
服务700到800的搜索引擎
million people in China and making it
中国有一百万人
the third largest ranch in the search
搜索中的第三大牧场
engine in the world and of course
世界上的引擎，当然
Netflix which in the primetime evening
在黄金时间傍晚的Netflix
hours the United States accounts for
美国占的小时数
something like the like eighty percent
大约百分之八十
of the Internet traffic these are all
这些都是互联网流量
companies that have also had to make
还必须制造的公司
this Trek and they've done so on top of
这次跋涉，他们除了
spring and invariably when you talk to
春天，总是和你说话
them you discovered they had to build a
他们你发现他们必须建立一个
layer on top to address this property's
顶层以解决此属性的
problems and so we've we're great
问题，所以我们很棒
admirers for example of Netflix they've
崇拜者，例如他们拥有的Netflix
built a lot of great stuff and they've
建立了很多很棒的东西，他们已经
open source a lot of it and we we would
开源很多，我们会
use that as an inspiration when we built
当我们建立时以此为灵感
something called spring cloud which
所谓的春天云
integrates allow those pieces as well as
集成允许这些部分以及
pieces from other technology stacks so
来自其他技术堆栈的碎片
what we're going to look at today is
我们今天要看的是
specifically the bits inside of spring
特别是弹簧里面的位
cloud again ignoring a lot of the other
云再次忽略了很多其他
features that spring cloud provide
Spring Cloud提供的功能
around security and distributed
围绕安全性和分布式
configuration and messaging and all that
配置和消息传递以及所有这些
we're going to look specifically at the
我们将专门研究
bits that can help you build robust
可以帮助您构建坚固的钻头
service to service interactions okay so
服务到服务的交互还可以
we're going to look at a project here
我们将在这里看一个项目
and by the by just so we're on the same
顺便说一句，我们在同一个
page you can follow along at home again
您可以再次在家跟随的页面
the code is on on my github github com
代码在我的github github com上
pornstache Josh longport / bootiful
色情影片乔什·朗波特/战利品
hyphen microservices ok so the code is
连字符微服务好，所以代码是
all there i'll be and fully fleshed out
我将要存在的全部充实
form what i have here is a but a
形式我在这里是一个但一个
skeleton husk of what we need i'm going
我要去的骨架
to stand up configuration service this
站起来配置服务
is just a sort of a proxy for
只是一种代理
configuration files by that I mean yeah
我的意思是配置文件
most files okay and these yamo files
大多数文件还可以，而这些yamo文件
live in my home directory and there in
住在我的主目录中
under a directory called beautiful
在名为beautiful的目录下
microservices config that that
微服务配置
repository if you like is also available
如果您愿意，还可以使用存储库
in my github repository am I gonna have
在我的github存储库中
account yeah and so you can clone those
是的，所以您可以克隆那些
as well I won't spend too much time
我也不会花太多时间
looking at these configuration files but
查看这些配置文件，但是
suffice it to say I'm not keeping the
足以说我没有保留
configuration along with the the modules
配置以及模块
here because it's it's a good way d
在这里，因为这是个好方法
couple in d &amp; D couple the configuration
d＆D夫妇一对配置
from the applications that consume it
从消耗它的应用程序中
this is better introduced in a previous
最好在前面介绍
webinar I've done on spring cloud and of
我在Spring Cloud和上完成的网络研讨会
course the reference documentation is
当然参考文档是
second to none and there's a blog you
首屈一指，有一个博客
might check if I may so humbly recommend
可能会检查我是否会如此谦虚地推荐
it it's one that I wrote to a few months
这是我写了几个月的书
ago called 12 fact wrap style
以前称为12事实环绕式
configuration and did a drive home the
配置，并开车回家
point here but the point is I've got it
指向这里，但关键是我明白了
in this application this an ensemble of
在此应用程序中
services and I need to stand up that
服务，我需要站起来
configuration server so I'll do so
配置服务器，所以我会这样做
spring food application at enables
启用春季食品应用
config server which I think it's already
我认为它已经是配置服务器
running retro
复古运行
it's not good
这不好
ok
好
you
您
I started two of them I think so i'll
我开始了其中两个，我想
just run again
再次运行
and then from here we can we can fairly
然后从这里我们可以公平地
well ignore first thing I need to do is
好吧，我要做的第一件事就是
stand up what is a phone book of service
站起来是什么服务电话簿
registry the idea that i want my
登记我想要我的想法
services which may you know grow any
您可能知道的任何服务都会增长
number to be able to discover each other
能够发现彼此的数字
right and in order to do that i want
对，为了做到这一点，我想要
them to be immune to topology changes
它们不受拓扑变化的影响
for example in the cloud environment
例如在云环境中
such as cloud foundry or Heroku or open
例如Cloud Foundry或Heroku或open
shift or or indeed just amazon web
转移或实际上只是亚马逊网络
services directly services are ephemeral
直接服务是短暂的
they come and go as capacity dictates
他们来来往往取决于容量
and where they live isn't so much isn't
他们住的地方不是很多
so important as the fact that they're
事实如此重要
available all right so that that that
可以使用，以便
bit of decoupling is typically
去耦位通常
accommodated through something called a
通过一个称为
service registry there are several
服务注册表有几个
different options out there Netflix have
Netflix有不同的选择
something called Eureka Eureka's their
叫做尤里卡（Eureka）的东西
service registry it's very very simple
服务注册表非常非常简单
to use Eureka in your application so
在您的应用程序中使用Eureka
we're going to go ahead and set up an
我们将继续进行并建立一个
instance of it here you need to get your
它的实例在这里，你需要得到你的
week a proper ignoring the configuration
一周适当忽略配置
bits and that's you know start for
一点，那你就知道开始了
another day but you get you week a
另一天，但你得到一个星期
proper you need spring cloud starter
正确的你需要Spring Cloud Starter
your weakest server and then you need a
您最弱的服务器，然后您需要一个
public static void main you'll say
你会说public static void main
Eureka application for example okay and
尤里卡应用程序，例如好和
I will cheat here
我会在这里作弊
what it looks like oops don't even need
看起来根本不需要
that okay so there's my your week
好的，那是我的一周
application it's going to set a stand-up
应用程序将设置一个站立
of service registry again this is the
服务注册表再次这是
important thing here right this is the
重要的是，这是
one annotation I need and it's going to
我需要一个注释，它将
stand up the registry based on netflixs
站起来基于netflixs的注册表
you because services you there are other
你，因为你有其他服务
options like console from hachey Corp
Hachey Corp的控制台等选项
the company that makes some vagrant and
那些无所事事的公司
surf and so on and there's also a zoo
冲浪等等，还有一个动物园
keeper Pepe zookeeper which is a very
饲养员佩佩动物园管理员，这是一个非常
very prolific court you know
你知道非常多产的法院
coordination registry very good as well
协调注册表也很好
and they're all available in highly
而且它们都高度可用
available modes in our case I'm just
在我们的情况下可用的模式
standing up one instance of Eureka
站起来一个尤里卡实例
you'll see as we work with it that it
您会在我们使用它的过程中看到它
doesn't like that it's going to
不喜欢它会
encourage you very loudly to a to
大声鼓励你去
reconsider the folly of your ways so 87
重新考虑自己的愚蠢方式87
61 there we are so there are no services
61我们在那里，所以没有服务
available here okay I haven't registered
在这里可用，好，我还没有注册
yet I haven't started any services yet
但我还没有开始任何服务
so that that's that let's make sense
这样才有意义
other than that though this is pretty
除此之外，虽然这很漂亮
basic you know wetware and the UI there
基本，您知道湿件和那里的U​​I
is also a REST API this is an indication
也是REST API，这表明
of the not liking my non highly
不喜欢我的非高度
available configuration the exception
可用配置例外
you see here is from the ears replica
你看这里是从耳朵复制品
available thing and that blows chunks
可用的东西，这吹大块
this is a wetware from the view of the
从这个角度来看，这是一个湿器
data but there's also a REST API for
数据，但还有一个REST API
machines okay and there is a in a theory
机器还可以，理论上有一个
cosmetics oh no I forget but there's a
化妆品哦，不，我忘了，但是有一个
there's an end point you can consume as
有一个终点可以作为
well you want to have to deal with that
好吧，你想处理
end point directly as well see but it is
终点也直接看到，但这是
their right so this is an API and
他们的权利，所以这是一个API，
services are going to register
服务将要注册
themselves in it and they'll be just
自己在里面，他们将只是
able to discover each other by service
能够通过服务发现彼此
ID here so about those services our
这里的ID，以便了解我们的那些服务
first one is going to be a bookmark
第一个将成为书签
service this is a service that will
服务这是一项服务，
maintain a collection of bookmark data
维护书签数据的集合
for us again not particularly
对我们来说又不是特别
fascinating but I just wanted to have
迷人，但我只想拥有
two different API level that will
两种不同的API级别
connect to
连接到
later on the bookmark service is a
稍后在书签服务上是
pretty boilerplate spring bootie
漂亮的样板春天短靴
application so let's say bookmark
应用程序，所以我们说书签
application like so and command jbm
像这样的应用程序和命令jbm
bookmark Java what you see here is
书签Java您在这里看到的是
fairly you know again pretty mundane
相当，你再次知道世界
right it's a public static void main so
对，这是一个公共的静态无效主体，所以
I've got spring application that run
我有运行的spring应用程序
this is spring boot i'm using the spring
这是 spring boot ，我正在使用弹簧
client application annotation which is
客户端应用程序注释是
to say i want this application to be a
说我希望这个应用程序是一个
spring boot app I'm going to I'm going
spring boot 应用程序，我要去
to enable the circuit circuit breaker
使电路断路器
and the discovery client this is a
和发现客户端，这是一个
client-side API for our service registry
我们的服务注册表的客户端API
in this case eureka i'm going to i have
在这种情况下，尤里卡我要去
a command line run right here the
命令行在这里运行
command line runner will start up excuse
命令行运行程序将启动借口
me this command line runner will start
我这个命令行运行程序将启动
up and they will create a bookmark for
起来，他们将为创建书签
every user so this collection this code
每个用户，所以此收集此代码
here will simply iterate through these
这里将简单地遍历这些
five different names and for each name
五个不同的名称，每个名称
user ID it'll create a bookmark object
用户ID，它将创建一个书签对象
for that that user so I'll have five
给那个用户，所以我有五个
bookmark objects in my database which in
在我的数据库中将对象添加为书签
this case is a h2 based database and
这种情况是基于H2的数据库，
i'll be using to spring data k peda to
我将用来将数据k peda转换为
save everything off I've got a rest
节省一切我休息
controller little export export to the
控制器出口少，出口到
bookmarks under the user ID afford such
用户ID下的书签提供了这样的功能
bookmarks okay Matt fairly mundane just
书签还可以吗Matt相当普通
of JP entity nothing particularly fancy
JP实体的名字没什么特别的
so let's run this it will register
所以让我们运行它会注册
itself in the broker using the name it
本身在经纪人中使用的名称
has been given in the bootstrap that
在引导程序中已经给出了
yamo properties file now this is a
yamo属性文件，现在这是一个
spring cloud ism this is a very similar
春天的云ism这是非常相似的
to spring boots propensity for loading
spring boot 的加载倾向
app application that you annual
您每年的应用程序应用程序
applications are property spring cloud
应用是财产春天云
willow bootstrap to emerald buddha
柳树引导到翡翠佛
chapter properties this is a file it
章节属性这是一个文件吗
gets loaded before the application
在应用程序之前加载
equivalent and that's because for
等价的，那是因为
example these are these values for
例如这些是这些值
example the spring cloud config your I
例子春天云配置你我
paths are needed for spring boot to load
弹簧引导加载所需的路径
properties for the rest of the
其余的属性
application to be configured so again
重新配置应用程序
don't want too much but all we care
不想太多，但我们在乎
about is that this is the ID of the
大约是这是
applique
贴花
and if we revisit Eureka will see that
如果我们重新访问尤里卡，将会看到
it is yes very very unhappy and it has
是的，非常非常不快乐，
been registered so the application is
已注册，因此该应用程序是
here bookmark service I can run another
在这里我可以运行另一个书签服务
instance of the bookmark service and
书签服务的实例和
again the reason I can do that is
再次我能做到的原因是
because i have not configured a server
因为我还没有配置服务器
that port by default and it's going to
默认情况下，该端口将
the config server and it's looking for
配置服务器，它正在寻找
configuration and the configuration you
配置和您的配置
know for the bookmark service doesn't
知道书签服务不
specifically specify anything for a port
专门为端口指定任何内容
so it's going to drop you know drop
所以它会掉落，你知道掉落
through to the default you know every
到您知道的每个默认值
man's property file called application
男人的属性文件称为应用程序
ammo and there i'll have a property
弹药，我在那里有财产
called server report which says if
称为服务器报告，其中指出
there's a port variable prefer that
有一个端口变量更喜欢
otherwise sort of a nested if else if
否则有点嵌套
there's a server port variable prefer
有一个服务器端口变量首选
that otherwise 0 and 0 in the case of
否则为0和0
spring boot means just assign me a
spring boot 意味着给我分配一个
random one so i can get away with this
随机一个，这样我就可以摆脱
chicanery on my local machine here so
我本地机器上的骗子
i'm going to run it again without any
我将再次运行它，没有任何
worries of collision and when we do that
碰撞的忧虑，以及当我们这样做时
okay in a few minutes or few seconds
几分钟或几秒钟就可以了
time we should see this status here
时间，我们应该在这里看到这种状态
which is up one increment from one to
从1到1是一个增量
two right that's that's pretty natural
两个是很自然的
the response is 200 so you can see it's
响应是200，所以您可以看到
already talking to you we go using the
已经与您交谈，我们将使用
heartbeat we just need for it to reflect
心跳，我们只需要它来反映
here and this information is valuable
在这里，这些信息很有价值
because now you know I want to be able
因为现在你知道我想要
to get all the instances available for
获取所有可用的实例
that that service era see it's a
那个服务时代看到了
discovery client bookmark service we
发现客户书签服务我们
registering apps bookmark service
注册应用书签服务
registering service registration status
注册服务注册状态
204 and
204和
apart
分开
you
您
did my
我的
that's interesting
那很有意思
I never actually tried for the same node
我从来没有尝试过相同的节点
I know it works on multiple nodes
我知道它可以在多个节点上运行
because definitely work from there oh
因为肯定从那里开始哦
well um so I guess that doesn't work on
好吧，所以我想那是行不通的
the same node anyway but anyway the
无论如何，但相同的节点
service is up there's the one that we
服务到了，有一个我们
wanted to talk about good I've killed
想谈谈我杀了的好东西
both of them in this case we run on that
他们两个在这种情况下，我们在
and then we'll move on to the next
然后我们继续下一个
service which is the DM contact service
DM联系服务
and the contact service very much like
和联系服务非常像
the bookmark service is just a an API
书签服务只是一个API
that will hold all of the contact
将保留所有联系人
information for different users ok so
为不同用户提供的信息还可以
I'll reinstate this module here contact
我将在此处恢复此模块
service
服务
I'm going to add a context context
我要添加一个上下文上下文
application
应用
you
您
okay and good there's also there's the
好的，很好，还有
contact
联系
location it's same thing as before I've
位置和我以前一样
got a command line runner it will start
有一个命令行运行器，它将开始
up in the spring good application starts
春季开始，良好的应用程序开始
up it can go through this collection of
可以通过这个集合
user IDs and then for each user it'll
用户ID，然后为每个用户
create one to three different context
创建一到三个不同的上下文
you know sort of like a phone book
你知道有点像电话簿
Maxwell phone book for each of these
麦克斯韦电话簿为这些
three different names and i'll save in
三个不同的名称，我将保存在
the database okay so now the only thing
数据库还好，所以现在唯一的事情
i'm going to use to correlate the
我将用来关联
request for changes to services is the
要求更改服务是
user ID the contacts and the bookmarks
用户ID联系人和书签
are both collections underneath the user
都在用户下方
ID view route okay again if you're using
如果您正在使用ID查看路线，可以再次使用
a in a more production oriented system
在面向生产的系统中
you'll use something else beside the
您将在
user ID in the URI paths for correlation
URI路径中用于关联的用户ID
you might use for example in the case of
例如，您可能会使用
a user context they might use a spring
用户上下文，他们可能会使用spring
cloud security access token right which
云安全访问令牌的权利
is an access token that spring cloud and
是春天出现的访问令牌
spring security all wats can make dead
春季安全，所有灾难都会使人丧命
simple to both stand up produce and
既容易站起来生产又
consume okay so that is here let's run
消耗好吧，让我们开始运行
this
这个
ok
好
services back fantastic the contact
服务回奇妙的联系
service should be up and running taking
服务应该启动并开始运行
this up and running here we go and give
在这里运行，我们去给
that a second we'll see it available the
一秒钟，我们将看到它可用
contact service the contact service just
联系服务只是联系服务
like the bookmark service exposes
就像书签服务暴露的那样
context underneath the user ID so the
用户ID下的上下文，因此
bookmark services under user ID for such
用户ID下的书签服务
bookmarks the contact services user ID
为联系服务用户标识添加书签
for such contacts as I say these are
我说的这些联系方式是
forced to engineer Quinn sentences you
强迫工程师奎因判你
might use an access token later on but
稍后可能会使用访问令牌，但是
in every other respect these services
在其他方面，这些服务
know nothing about each other right this
彼此一无所知吧
is very common in a service-oriented
在面向服务中非常常见
world you might look at programmable all
世界，你可能会看所有可编程的
the different services that sign in with
用来登录的不同服务
Facebook you know they don't actually
Facebook，你知道他们实际上并没有
have their own their own sort of ID or
有自己的ID或
notion of identity for you as a user
您作为用户的身份概念
they have the ID that they're sharing
他们有他们共享的ID
with with Facebook or by extension the
与Facebook或扩展
access token that they're sharing with
访问他们共享的令牌
Facebook which is as good as an ID so
和ID一样好的Facebook
now both the bookmark service in the
现在，两者中的书签服务
contact service of automatically
自动联系服务
register themselves the way that they're
以自己的方式注册自己
able to do that is each one each one of
能够做到的是每个一个
these modules again very very simple
这些模块又非常非常简单
spring boot style services here's my web
spring boot 式服务，这是我的网站
support my configuration client support
支持我的配置客户端支持
we don't either this is that but a
我们不是不是那个而是
spring boots support for jpa the
spring boot 支持JPA
actuator bits for the management metrics
用于管理指标的执行器位
endpoints and Eureka in particular this
端点和尤里卡尤其如此
is the Eureka module a client-side
Eureka模块是客户端
support right before it was you week a
在您一周之前就提供支持
server here's Eureka this is going to
服务器在这里是Eureka
provide a spring boot auto configuration
提供spring boot自动配置
that will take the current applications
将采用当前的应用程序
bring that up location that name contact
带出姓名联系的地点
the Eureka service registry and again
Eureka服务注册表，然后再次
it's going to do that by looking for the
它会通过寻找
configuration it's got in the config
配置在配置中
server in this case I've got you know
在这种情况下，我知道你的服务器
all my nodes that will need to talk to
我需要与之交谈的所有节点
you week are going to need the same
你这一周将需要同样的
value so I put that in application that
价值，所以我把它放在应用程序中
yellow and then all my services share
黄色，然后我所有的服务共享
application that yamo and they're going
yamo和他们要去的应用程序
to call Eureka client service URL
调用尤里卡客户服务URL
default zone and this is the you know
默认区域，这是您所知道的
property placeholder resolution
财产占位符解析
mechanism that's going to be used to
该机制将用于
locate the registry I'm going to either
找到我要去的注册表
try and resolve it via this environment
尝试通过此环境解决它
this environment property or if if I
这个环境财产，或者如果我
properties absent this literal Oklahoma
俄克拉荷马州没有这个属性
colon 8760 one okay so that's that's how
冒号8760一个好吧，那就是这样
I'm guaranteeing that spring clamp that
我保证那个弹簧夹
each spring cloud microservice is able
每个Spring Cloud微服务都能够
to find the registration registered off
查找已注册的注册
with one steps up and running I will
一步一步地运行，我会
also have the ability to for example in
也有能力例如
my code inject and each one of these
我的代码注入以及其中的每一个
services i can actually inject a void
服务我实际上可以注入一个空白
asset instance instance info
资产实例实例信息
alright for example I'm using beacon
好吧，例如，我正在使用信标
this case and I can use the info to get
这种情况下，我可以使用信息来获取
metadata and I can actually set values
元数据，我实际上可以设置值
in there or I can read values right this
在那里，我也可以读取值
is the object that spring cloud is going
是春天的云去的对象
to configure this for this specific
为此配置此
instance for this specific node I can
我可以为此特定节点的实例
actually add metadata I can say oh well
实际添加元数据我可以说哦
you know cookie or something like that
你知道饼干或类似的东西
or whatever i want right i can say i can
或者我想说的任何我可以说的
add metadata to the registry that i can
将元数据添加到注册表中
then query later on right so this is
然后稍后在右边查询，这是
actually a very very powerful pattern
实际上是一个非常非常强大的模式
and i can use that metadata to sort of
我可以使用该元数据来
demarcate the kind of service set of
划分服务集的种类
specific node supports or the role that
特定节点支持的角色或
it plays okay now let's finally build a
现在可以正常播放了
passport service or passport service
护照服务或护照服务
will be it'll be a client sort of an
它将是客户的一种
aggregation point for our Spring cloud
我们的Spring云的聚集点
microservices the passport service will
微服务护照服务将
work with both contacts and bookmarks
使用联系人和书签
ok
好
and it's a fairly straightforward BM
这是一个相当简单的BM
desperate Java there's actually a fair
绝望的Java实际上是公平的
man going on here so we'll walk to it
男人继续在这里，所以我们会走向它
one by one what I'm trying to do what
一件一件地做我想做的事
I'm trying to demonstrate is how to
我试图证明是如何
consume other services okay and so I've
可以使用其他服务，所以我已经
got to spring spring boot in spring tide
在春季潮中赶上 spring boot
application of course I've turn on
我已经打开了应用程序
netflix is fain and zoo we'll come back
netflix很不高兴，动物园我们会回来的
to both of these in just a minute but
只需一分钟即可
done that if you know should look from
这样做，如果你知道应该从
fairly familiar the what we're going to
相当熟悉我们要做什么
do is we're going to use that command
要做的是我们将使用该命令
line winner remember this is the
线赢家记得这是
interface that I showed earlier it has
我之前显示的界面
one job given the public static void
鉴于公共静态空缺，一份工作
main string argument or a that gets
主字符串参数或获取
passed into the run method do something
传递给run方法做某事
right and this gets called after the
对的，这个在
spring application I started it's not
我开始的春季申请不是
it's if initializing bean is a way to
如果初始化bean是一种方法
configure a bean after it's been
经过配置的bean
configured command line where is a way
配置命令行，哪里有办法
to do processing after the application
申请后做处理
has been configured and so it's a great
已经配置了，所以很棒
place to put some demo code so the first
放置一些演示代码的地方，所以第一个
instance of the command line runner that
命令行运行程序的实例
we're going to have here is something
我们将要在这里有一些东西
that uses the spring cloud commons
使用Spring Cloud Commons
discovery client now again the discovery
发现客户端现在再次发现
client is the client-side API as an
客户端是客户端API
abstraction that's common to all the
所有这些都通用的抽象
different supported service registries
不同的支持服务注册表
that spring cloud knows about and it
那春天的云知道并且
allows us to ask questions of the
允许我们提出有关
service registry so in this case we're
服务注册表，因此在这种情况下，我们
going to get an implementation and in
将得到一个实施和
fact you'll you can guess which one it
事实上你会猜到哪一个
is if you look at the available
如果你看看可用的
implementations on the classpath we're
我们在类路径上的实现
going to get an implementation of Eureka
将要实现尤里卡
discovery client although we don't we
发现客户，尽管我们不是
don't know that because at runtime we're
不知道，因为在运行时
gonna have the interface type if I had
如果我有接口类型
if I were using spring cloud support for
如果我使用Spring Cloud支持
console i would get that implementation
控制台我会实现
if i were using spring clouds support
如果我正在使用Spring Cloud支持
for zookeeper i would get that
对于动物园管理员，我会得到的
implementation if i were using spring
如果我正在使用spring的实现
cloud support for lattice distributed
云对网格分布式的支持
runtime i would get that implementation
运行时我会实现
or for cloud foundry i would get that
或对于云铸造，我会得到的
implementation etc and once i've done
实施等，一旦我完成
that i get i can make calls against the
我得到我可以打电话反对
the discovery client i can say discovery
我可以说发现客户
client i get instances this returns a
客户端我得到实例，这返回一个
list of service instance objects and
服务实例对象列表和
that service those service instances are
这些服务实例是服务
again that's an interface so i'll get an
再次，这是一个界面，所以我会得到一个
implementation specific to eureka
尤里卡特有的实施
or to console or to whatever and I can
或控制台或任何我可以
ask questions like what is a service
提出诸如服务之类的问题
idea the host support etc for a given
主意给定的主机支持等
service and I can articulate information
服务，我可以表达信息
about that service so
关于这项服务
here we go
开始了
you
您
okay so then we're going to print out
好，那么我们将要打印出来
for each service I'll print out the host
对于每项服务，我都会打印出主机
port and so on from the service registry
服务注册表中的端口等
the phone book if you will okay and of
电话簿，如果您还可以的话
course in our case we've only got one
当然，在我们的情况下，我们只有一个
registered instance of each so you'll
每个的注册实例，因此您将
see only one 1 entry be printed out here
此处仅显示1个条目
okay small screen along the line of code
好的，沿着代码行的小屏幕
problems sorry about that folks okay
问题对不起那个人好吗
here we go so that's probably the first
在这里，我们可能是第一个
thing we can see that will actually
我们可以看到的东西实际上
that's a programmatic way of asking
这是一种程序化的询问方式
questions about the topology of the
有关拓扑的问题
cluster is the service available if so
群集是否可用（如果有）
how many instances are there and you
你有多少个实例
know what other metadata can you give me
知道你还能给我什么其他元数据
I can of course downcast my service
我当然可以贬低我的服务
instance to a beam of type Eureka
实例到尤里卡类型的光束
service instance if I know that that's
服务实例，如果我知道那是
the type I got that and all that's the
我得到的类型就是
type i'm going to get moving up sort of
类型，我将开始向上移动
the abstraction hierarchy a little bit
抽象层次结构
let's let's turn to instead of manually
让我们转向而不是手动
extracting the host import and then
提取主机导入，然后
feeding that into some other
喂到其他
communication mechanism we understand
我们了解的沟通机制
that in this case I'm trying to make API
在这种情况下，我正在尝试制作API
calls to another ref service right so I
呼叫另一个参考服务，所以我
don't really need I don't really need
真的不需要我真的不需要
just the host important I just want to
只是重要的主机，我只想
make a rest call and I have of course
打个电话，我当然有
Springs rest template which makes a dead
弹簧休息模板，使人死亡
simple common HTTP calls right get
简单的常见HTTP调用正确获取
posted cetera or the more general
发布的cetera或更一般的
purpose exchange which let's make an
目的交流，让我们
HTTP call against a rest service so i'm
针对休息服务的HTTP调用，所以我
going to use the rest template it's a
要使用其余模板，这是一个
you know it's got the ability you can
你知道它有能力
configure interceptors and those
配置拦截器和那些
interceptors can pre process and post
拦截器可以进行预处理和发布
process HTTP requests and spring cloud
处理HTTP请求和Spring Cloud
will automatically configure an
将自动配置
interceptor that will look at the URL
拦截器将查看URL
that we're trying to make the call
我们正在尝试拨打电话
against and then see that we're actually
反对，然后看到我们实际上
not referencing a host here this is
这里没有引用主机
bookmark hyphen service this is a
书签连字符服务，这是一个
service ID and indeed the same service
服务ID和确实相同的服务
ideas we have in Eureka okay so it's
我们在尤里卡（Eureka）有想法，所以
going to pre-process this it's going to
要对此进行预处理
pluck that out it's going to call you
摘下它会打电话给你
eeka it's going to get back a collection
eeka它会取回一个收藏
of service instances in our case we'll
在我们的案例中，我们将
only have one but as you register more
只有一个，但是当您注册更多时
and more you'll get 10 20 100 whatever
甚至更多，您将获得10 20 100
and then it'll try and pick from among
然后尝试从中选择
those instances the the best instance to
这些实例是最好的实例
respond to the call and then little
接听电话，然后很少
forward request to that instance now
现在将请求转发到该实例
this is of course a very important point
这当然是非常重要的一点
how does it determine which instance to
它如何确定要哪个实例
use it's going to use something called
使用它会使用称为
ribbon from also from netflix ribbon is
来自netflix功能区的功能区是
a software-defined load bouncer
软件定义的负载弹跳器
it provides the ability to encode apply
它提供了编码申请的能力
her some sort of heuristic to pick from
她从某种启发式选择
among a set of instances there are a lot
在一组实例中，有很多
of reasons why you might do this sort of
为什么您会这样做的原因
routing in the client in Java code as
用Java代码在客户端中进行路由
opposed to perhaps at the big five
反对也许在五巨头
router f5 router a no
路由器F5路由器A否
most of the the reasons that i can give
我可以给出的大多数原因
you center around the idea that the
您围绕着这个想法
client is in a better position to
客户处于更好的位置
respond to the unique oddities of your
回应您的独特怪异
topology changes not the router right
拓扑更改不是路由器正确
and the client and the code are in the
客户端和代码在
best position to change it and make sure
更改并确保最佳位置
it works accordingly I keep the code
它相应地工作，我保留代码
keep the routing rules in the
将路由规则保留在
application itself indeed I may consume
应用程序本身确实可以消耗
an application with it in a totally
一个带有它的应用程序
different pattern than some other
与其他模式不同
applications same API but different
应用程序相同的API但不同
different use cases different sort of
不同的用例，不同的
routing rules and ribbon has lots of
路由规则和功能区有很多
defined aristocrat faults we're going to
我们将要定义的贵族错误
get one that's going to give us a round
得到一个可以给我们回合的机会
robin dispatch but I can plug in my own
罗宾调度，但我可以自己插入
and I might for example use one of the
例如，我可能会使用其中之一
out of the box routers I might choose
开箱即用的路由器，我可能会选择
for example to care about availability
例如关心可用性
zones or I might decide I want to have a
区，否则我可能会决定我想要一个
router that routes calls to the specific
路由呼叫到特定的路由器
cluster of services or to a specific
服务集群或特定的
data center or whatever right or i can
数据中心或其他任何权利，或者我可以
pick something else i might have some
选择别的东西我可能会有一些
concept again predicated on that
概念再次基于此
metadata map for example perhaps that
元数据映射例如
you know so that this node is a master
您知道这个节点是主节点
that one's a worker or something like
那是一个工人或类似的东西
that right again that is entirely up to
再次完全取决于
you you can override the algorithm that
您可以覆盖该算法
that ribbon uses by overriding the load
功能区通过覆盖负载使用的
balancer client object that a spring
弹簧的平衡器客户端对象
cloud automatically configures for you
云自动为您配置
so again this is a regular spring boot
再次，这是一个常规的 spring boot
is emits a beam that having a
发出的光束具有
conditional conditional on missing beam
有条件的，有条件的
annotation so if you define a beam of
注解，因此，如果您定义
the same type that'll be preferred
与首选相同的类型
instead of this one and that's what will
而不是这个，那将是
get passed into into the rest template
传递到其余模板中
interceptor that eventually processes
最终处理的拦截器
this call other notable things of course
这当然是其他值得注意的事情
is that we're making a rest call i'm
是我们正在打个电话
making an exchange call i'm asking it
打个电话我要问
for a list of bookmark types back
返回书签类型列表
this bookmark is the same it's not the
这个书签是一样的，不是
same focus we saw earlier in the
我们先前在
bookmark service it's a type i have in
书签服务，这是我的一种类型
the same code page it is not a JP entity
不是JP实体的同一代码页
and has nothing to do with the other
与其他无关
type and that maybe you know that that's
类型，也许您知道那是
because my other service may for example
因为例如我的其他服务
be implemented and you know might not be
被实施，你知道可能不会
using JP who knows now my other service
使用现在知道我其他服务的JP
is just as far as i know i just have
据我所知
json so this is the type on a map to
json，所以这是地图上的类型
Jason structure to you could of course
Jason的结构当然可以
if you have a more homogeneous
如果你有一个更均匀的
environment keep the type sort of
环境保持类型
details if you will in a separate jar
如果您要放在一个单独的罐子中，则会显示详细信息
people keep asking about that but i
人们一直在问这个，但我
would i would try not to do that first
我会尽量不要先这样做吗
and only if you have to then do it right
而且只有当你必须做正确的时候
so moving back up here
所以回到这里
the the information I want is I want to
我想要的信息是我想要的
list of bookmarks we know that that's
我们知道的书签列表
what I get back if i visit the passport
如果我看护照我会得到什么
service so for example if i go here or
服务，例如，如果我去这里或
rather if i go to the bookmark service
如果我去书签服务
that go here and then i go to p web
那去这里然后我去p网
forward slash bookmarks I get you know
正斜杠书签我知道
when i get a collection of one element
当我得到一个元素的集合
this one element here for the p web link
这是p网站链接的一个元素
and i want to get that in a list right i
我想把它放在清单中
have to use a hack this is a sort of a
必须使用hack，这是一种
nasty thing that we have to do in java
我们必须在Java中做的令人讨厌的事情
because of type or Asia this is an
由于类型或亚洲，这是一个
implementation of the pattern called the
模式的实现称为
type token pattern java doesn't have the
类型令牌模式Java没有
ability at runtime for an instance
实例在运行时的功能
variable to true reflection tell you
真正反射的变量告诉您
what its generic type is right so this
它的通用类型是正确的，所以这
list of bookmark that disappears at one
消失的书签列表
time java thinks that this parameterize
时间java认为这参数化
type reference object is a parametrized
类型引用对象是参数化的
type reference of nothing or of object
没有或对象的类型引用
or if you well I mean it's there is no
或者如果你很好我的意思是那没有
generic parameter here it's a compiler
通用参数，这里是编译器
time only the piece of sugars well as a
时间只有一块糖以及
feature so in order to circumvent that
因此，为了规避
we can create an anonymous inner class
我们可以创建一个匿名内部类
subclasses that is to say if I could if
子类，即是否可以
I said class X extends parametrized type
我说X类扩展了参数化类型
reference of list you know like this
您知道这样的列表的引用
did that that actually retains as i can
这样做实际上保留了我可以
i can actually ask the instance X at
我实际上可以问实例X
runtime what its types its generic type
运行时的类型及其通用类型
is and it will be able to give me that
是的，它将能够给我
information so I'm doing the same thing
信息，所以我在做同样的事情
here i'm creating an anonymous subtype
在这里我正在创建一个匿名子类型
and that's the pattern right if i remove
如果我删除，这就是正确的模式
it in fact the spring privatized type
实际上是春季私有化类型
reference implementation of the type
该类型的参考实现
token pattern won't even let me compile
令牌模式甚至不让我编译
it's abstract so it requires that it be
它是抽象的，所以要求它是
a subclass okay and then I pass that
一个子类好吧，然后我通过
response type into the exchange method
响应类型转换为交换方法
and spring MVC address template and will
和Spring MVC地址模板，并将
pass it into the spring MVC message
将其传递给spring MVC消息
converts that I have configured on the
转换我在
client it'll say oh well we want to get
客户会说，哦，我们想得到
a list of bookmarks back can you think
您能想到的书签列表吗
convert this buffer in this case JSON
在这种情况下转换此缓冲区为JSON
into its that object the jackson message
将杰克逊消息放入该对象
converter will kick in and and then
转换器将启动，然后
it'll give us a response entity with a
它会给我们一个带有
payload of type list bookmarks okay so
类型列表书签的有效负载可以吗
this is the body that's the list of
这是身体的清单
bookmarks and i'm just going to print
书签，我将要打印
them all out here moving further up the
他们都在这里进一步向上
stack i'm going to use fain fain as
堆栈，我将使用fain fain作为
netflix is declarative rest client
netflix是声明式其余客户端
technology it's sort of like the spring
技术有点像春天
data repositories it's a based on
它基于的数据存储库
interfaces I can declaratively describe
我可以声明式描述的接口
the contract for a rest service so here
休息服务合同，所以在这里
I'm saying here's a Java interface that
我是说这是一个Java接口
will be a client-side representation of
将是的客户端表示
a a rest service and when I I'm going to
休息服务，当我要去
use the pain client annotation i'm going
使用我要去的痛苦客户注释
to plug in the bookmark service i'm
插入我的书签服务
going to you know spend some other i
去你知道我花了一些我
want to use the bookmark service as
想要将书签服务用作
discovered from your week again it'll
再次从您的一周中发现
it'll look up the instances from your
它将从您的实例中查找实例
week and pass them into ribbon I want to
一周，将它们传递给我想要的功能区
use that service to handle this request
使用该服务来处理此请求
and then I want to call forward slash
然后我想叫正斜杠
user ID forward slash bookmarks and for
用户ID正斜杠书签和
the book book for the user ID parameter
用户ID参数的书
I'm going to pass and they get book more
我要过去了，他们得到更多的书
excuse ER ID parameter from the method
从方法中借用ER ID参数
okay so same thing for the contact
好吧，联络人也一样
service here you know you have almost no
服务在这里，你知道你几乎没有
idea at all from their consumer
消费者的想法
perspective that this is HTTP this is
观点，这是HTTP，这是
actually much much higher level than the
实际上比
HTTP centric rest template and the low
以HTTP为中心的休息模板和低端
level discovery client and Dirk approach
级别发现客户端和Dirk方法
down here right
在这里
and we've gotten you know you can choose
我们已经知道您可以选择
whatever approach whatever granularity
无论采用何种方法，无论粒度如何
works best for you the results will
最适合您的结果
always be you know it'll we don't work
永远是你知道这会我们不工作
either way you'll get the result if you
无论哪种方式，如果您获得结果，
want there's no reason I couldn't have
希望我没有理由
taken the discovery plan and extracted
采取了发现计划并提取了
the hosted port and then build up the
托管端口，然后建立
URL and plug that into the rest template
URL并将其插入其余模板
for example fine okay so let's start
例如好吧，让我们开始吧
this service up
这项服务
up in a way the service is also a I've
在某种程度上，服务也是我所拥有的
also exposed another resting point on
也暴露了另一个休息点
this service it's called the passport
这项服务叫做护照
end point and the point here is to two
终点，这里的重点是两个
in one place return an object that has
在一个地方返回一个具有
both the users context and the users
用户上下文和用户
bookmarks it's a sort of passport
收藏这是一种护照
passport object for context and
上下文的护照对象和
bookmarks for this user and i'm using
此用户的书签，我正在使用
i'm doing this in officially in the name
我正式以这个名义
of simplicity of code in the demo here
演示中的代码简单性
but i would recommend for any anything
但我会推荐任何东西
non-trivial make these two different
不平凡使这两个不同
poles which are of course network ops
电线杆当然是网络运营商
concurrent and you can very easily do
并发，您可以很容易地做到
that using something like RX java so i
那使用RX Java之类的东西，所以我
can use RX travel to say that I want
可以用RX旅行说我想要
this call and that is a call to happen
这个电话，那是发生的电话
concurrently and then I want to I want
同时，然后我想要
to zip in and then process the results
压缩然后处理结果
at the same time you know once they're
同时你知道他们一旦
both returned so I'm going to use that
都回来了，所以我要用那个
eight endpoint here I can go to Eureka
八个终点在这里我可以去尤里卡
and find out that the passport service
并发现护照服务
is now up and running it's on port 507
现在启动并运行在端口507上
17 and I go to jail on passport or p web
17，我因护照或个人证件入狱
if you will or these
如果您愿意或这些
air so again behind the scenes ok
空气，然后在幕后再次确定
bookmarks that's a rest call to the
书签，这是对
bookmark service and I've got context
书签服务，我有上下文
and again the contacts are coming from
再次联系人来自
another service i'm getting results here
我在这里得到结果的另一项服务
in a sort of aggregate entity called the
在一种称为
passport but those no reason this
护照，但没有理由
couldn't have been adapted and
不可能被改编，
transformed either right that's that's
改变了要么就是那个
certainly true so I want I want my
当然是真的，所以我想要我想要我的
services to be resilient to failure so
服务对失败具有弹性
for example what happens if I go to the
例如，如果我去
bookmark service and there's no service
书签服务，没有服务
available right what I don't want it to
可以使用我不想要的功能
just blow chunks and to throw its hands
只是吹大块，然后举起手
up in the air and quit so instead i can
悬而未决，所以我可以
use hystrix this is a implementation of
使用hystrix这是一个实现
the circuit breaker pattern and this
断路器模式和这个
implementation in particular is from
实施尤其来自
from netflix and it's basically going to
来自netflix，基本上
wrap this method around with a little
将此方法包装一点
stateful with a stateful state machine
有状态的状态机
with a little state machine that's going
带有一个小状态机
to say okay well the last attempted
说好吧，最后一次尝试
execution of this method invocation this
此方法的执行调用this
method create an exception
方法创建异常
if it fails and more times then
如果失败并且更多次
quarantine it make it so that you know
隔离它使您知道
nobody can call that method directly
没有人可以直接调用该方法
anymore instead route traffic to the
而是将流量路由到
fallback method so the fallback method
后备方法，所以后备方法
here is get bookmarked fall back it will
这是获得书签后退的它将
simply return an empty array and to
只需返回一个空数组并
empty a list of bookmark in this case
在这种情况下，清空书签列表
there's a gentleman another UK named
还有一个绅士，另一个英国
Fred George he gives a great talk about
弗雷德·乔治（Fred George）他发表了精彩的演讲
this he describes the human body as a
他将人体描述为
micro service system and it gives us
微服务系统，它给了我们
great idea that and I see this great
好主意，我看到这很棒
great suggest or illustration if I cut
如果我切的话很好的建议或插图
my hand I don't want the whole body to
我的手，我不想整个身体
just blue screen right I want I I can
只是蓝屏我想我可以
degrade gracefully I may bleed locally
优雅降级，我可能会在本地流血
but the whole thing doesn't just stop
但是整个事情并不会停止
working and service your system is a
工作和服务您的系统是一个
whole should be similar to that right so
整体应该类似于该权利，所以
here if something goes wrong I'll get a
如果出问题了，我会得到一个
default you know if the net if the
默认情况下，您知道网是否
netflix search engine is down for
netflix搜索引擎因
example i may get recommendations
例如我可能会得到建议
instead but you know i'll get something
相反，但是你知道我会得到一些东西
you know that's that's the point ok so
你知道那是重点，所以
this code of course is in my integration
这个代码当然在我的整合中
client and integration client is when
客户和集成客户是什么时候
i'm using my fain example i'm sorry in
我使用我的简单例子，对不起
my passport rest controller so the rest
我的护照管理员
controller is injecting the integration
控制器正在注入集成
client integration client is using the
客户端集成客户端正在使用
same implementations and i've got two
相同的实现，我有两个
different methods that make potentially
不同的方法可能
shaky network calls using the fame
摇摇欲坠的网络通话
clients and if something goes wrong they
客户，如果出现问题，他们
have backups i also have up here you'll
有备份，我也有备份，你会
recall they zool proxy ok so zool is an
记得他们是zoul代理人，所以zool是一个
api gateway so i don't know how good
api网关，所以我不知道有多好
your with your mythology or your
你的神话或你的
Ghostbusters lower but a zoo is the
捉鬼敢死队较低，但动物园是
gatekeeper it's this guy right here and
看门人就是这个家伙，
it's the creature that the gatekeeper
这是看门人的生物
right and this is a gate zool in ghosts
对，这是一个幽灵般的大门
and in sorry zool in the spring
在春天对不起动物
cloudstack is a implementation in the
cloudstack是
micro proxy pattern it's a reverse proxy
微代理模式，它是反向代理
that acts that sits at the edge of any
位于任何边缘的行为
of a service API something that you'll
一个服务API，您将获得
expose
暴露
to clients like a mobile device or an
给诸如移动设备或
html5 device and it will take requests
html5设备，它将接受请求
and proxy them to back-end services like
并将它们代理到后端服务，例如
for example the book park service or the
例如图书寄存服务或
contact service so I didn't have to do
联系服务，所以我不必做
anything to get working beside saying at
除了在...上说什么要工作
naval zool proxy it'll automatically
海军Zool代理，它将自动
talk to the service registry in this
在此与服务注册表对话
case eureka or consular zookeeper
尤里卡或领事动物园管理员
whatever and make those services
并提供这些服务
available underneath my roots of my
在我的根源下
passport service so I can go now to
护照服务，所以我现在可以去
contact service /p web for / contacts
联系服务/ p网站/联系
did I make a mistake here contact
我在这里弄错了吗联系
service there we go I was on the wrong
服务那里我们去我错了
interested wrong wrecker service so here
感兴趣的错误清障车服务，所以在这里
is the contact information coming from
联系信息来自
the back end contact service if i go to
后端联系服务，如果我去
bookmark service
书签服务
bookmark so again this part of the
再次添加书签
request is what I would have sent it to
请求就是我发送给的
the bookmark service route if I were
书签服务路线（如果我是
talking to that node and that post
与那个节点和那个帖子交谈
import directly but remember I'm on my
直接导入，但请记住我在
passport service here so I have to spend
这里的护照服务，所以我不得不花钱
to buy the service ID as the root here
在这里购买服务ID作为根
and it's very convenient for example if
例如，如果
I have an html5 client or something that
我有一个html5客户端或其他
has to run it can't run afoul of for
必须运行它不能违背
example class origin request forgery
类源请求伪造示例
restrictions and I don't want to read I
限制，我不想读我
don't want to retrofit every one of my
不想改造我的每一个人
existing microservices my back-end
现有的微服务后端
mid-tier microservices to be aware of
中级微服务要注意
these nuances of each client so instead
每个客户的这些细微差别
when a netflix does they stand up an API
netflix何时支持API
gateway an edge a micro proxy like zool
网关边缘像zool的微型代理
for every one of the clients that way
这样的每一位客户
even if they've got 600 different
即使他们有600种不同
mid-tier services the edge services are
中层服务边缘服务是
the ones that clients send traffic to
客户端向其发送流量的
and the edge services are not discovered
并且没有发现边缘服务
to you weak those are stood up and made
对你软弱的人站起来造出来
statically available to DNS they don't
静态提供给DNS，而他们没有
you know you can you can put those and
你知道你可以把那些和
wrap those and load down souls in your
包起来，把灵魂放进你的
router but the requests that those edge
路由器，但那些边缘的要求
services make to the mid-tier services
服务到中间层服务
in the background those are resolved
在后台解决了
through Eureka okay or the service
通过尤里卡还是可以的
registry so I've got two different ways
注册表，所以我有两种不同的方式
of consuming these back-end services as
使用这些后端服务的方式
we've seen I've got the Zulu proxy in
我们已经看到我有Zulu代理
play and I've got my passport service
玩，我有护照服务
which aggregates and consumes both
聚集并消耗两者
back-end services using something like
后端服务使用类似
Spain what happens you know we will talk
西班牙，发生什么事，您知道我们会谈
about that circuit breaker what happens
关于那个断路器会发生什么
if the bookmark service is gone for
如果书签服务消失了
example so if i go to the bookmark
例如，如果我转到书签
application and i'm going to exit it i'm
应用程序，我要退出它我
not sure if you can see then your screen
不确定是否可以看到屏幕
here but i'm hovering over the exit icon
在这里，但我将鼠标悬停在退出图标上
in IntelliJ so goodbye to bookmark
在IntelliJ中再见了
service I go to Eureka and refresh you
服务，我去尤里卡，给你刷新
can see it's already been deregistered
可以看到它已经被注销了
from their industry and now if I hit
从他们的行业，现在如果我打
refresh on the service you can see that
刷新服务，您可以看到
I get an empty collection back right so
我得到一个空的收藏，所以
that's exactly what we want we want it
这正是我们想要的，我们想要的
to be resilient to the topology changes
适应拓扑变化
ok I have of course I want to see what
好的，我当然想看看
this what's happening here so I want to
这是怎么回事，所以我想
be able to get a dashboard perspective
能够获得仪表板的角度
of what is happening for that
这是怎么回事
I've made it very easy to stand up with
我已经很容易站起来
dashboard appropriately called the
仪表板适当地称为
historic stash board I'm going to go
我要去的历史性藏板
ahead and also stand that up here we go
向前，也站在那里，我们去
okay good and it's just at naval history
好的，这只是在海军历史上
dashboard and run
仪表板并运行
this will this will let me
这将使我
by the individual node that has the
由具有
circuit in this case our passport
在这种情况下巡回我们的护照
service and
服务和
then I can ask it to consume the server
然后我可以要求它消耗服务器
send event stream called sir mr. extreme
发送事件流，称为先生先生。极端
that's being emitted from the passport
是从护照上散发的
service and if i go to my browser for
服务，如果我转到浏览器查看
example here's mr. extreme
例如这里的先生。极端
and it's just it'll never finish loading
只是它永远不会完成加载
right it is by definition an unending
对，根据定义，它是无止境的
stream of data so I'm going to tell
数据流，所以我要告诉
hystrix about my about my service it's
关于我的关于我的服务的hystrix
on port 500 817 localhost 508 17 for
在端口500817本地主机508 17上
such hystrix HTML and I'm going to
这样的hystrix HTML，我要
specify where to find the stream okay in
指定在哪里可以找到流
this case from the password service so
这种情况来自密码服务
hit monitor and you can see it's got an
点击监视器，您会看到它有一个
idea of the circuits in the system so
系统中电路的想法
get get bookmarks and then get contacts
获取书签，然后获取联系人
down here let's see if I can show both
在这里，让我看看是否可以同时显示两个
of these in action so
这些在行动，所以
you
您
get bookmarks good contacts here's my
获取书签，好的联系人，这是我的
passport it has both bookmarks in
护照上都有两个书签
context of course I've since taken the
从那以后，我当然会考虑
bookmark servers offline if I hit
如果我点击，则将书签服务器离线
refresh you'll see that as I hit refresh
刷新，当我点击刷新时，您会看到
I'm not sure if you can sit on the
我不确定你是否可以坐在
screen but I'm hitting refresh fairly
屏幕，但我正在刷新
heavily on my passport service here as I
像我一样，我非常重视我的护照服务
make requests the traffic spikes up here
在这里发出请求，流量激增
and you can see that the good get
你会看到好的收获
contacts circuit is working just fine
触点电路工作正常
it's a moving average so as I lay off
这是一个移动平均线，所以我裁员
the gas the traffic drains down but the
车辆排空的汽油，但
get bookmarks circuit is in trouble it's
获取书签电路有麻烦了
open and again you know this makes sense
再次打开，你知道这很有意义
right it's very much like a circuit
对，非常像电路
breaker in a house I'd much rather lose
我宁愿输掉房子里的断路器
the lights in the house to get it on
屋子里的灯开着
fire if I bring back the bookmark
如果我带回书签，则触发
application look so run
应用程序看起来如此运行
eventually that we register itself in
最终，我们在
Eureka and as soon as it does i'll be
尤里卡（Eureka），我会尽快
able to hit refresh and see that the
能够点击刷新并看到
circuit has been closed again and
电路再次关闭，
everything is hunky-dory this is a note
一切都是笨拙的，这是一个音符
by note view but i can use something
通过笔记视图，但我可以使用一些东西
called turbine and turbine will
叫做涡轮，涡轮会
aggregate a set of different streams and
聚合一组不同的流，并且
then present them to me in a single
然后把它们呈现给我
dashboard for anna tambo of services so
安娜·坦博（Ana Tambo）的服务仪表板
with that I think we've covered a lot
我认为我们已经涵盖了很多
we've looked
我们已经看过
at using spring cloud to consume
在使用春季云消耗
services simply with the likes of things
随心所欲地服务
like the rest template integration with
像其他模板一样
the discovery client with decoupled
分离的发现客户端
topology from availability using service
使用服务从可用性获取拓扑
registries like you weekend hystrix I'm
像你这样的注册表，周末我要
sorry weekend console zookeeper we've
抱歉，我们周末的动物园管理员
made our services more robust to outages
使我们的服务更能应对停机
using the circuit breaker pattern for
将断路器模式用于
example and and the service registration
示例和服务注册
and so on we've I didn't show you a
等等，我们没给你看
reactive code as you might implement it
您可能实现的反应式代码
with a RX Java but that's definitely
使用RX Java，但这绝对是
something I encourage you to check out
我鼓励您检查的东西
we could and probably should do a whole
我们可以并且可能应该做一个整体
webinar on just that if you have I you
网络研讨会只是说如果你有我的话
know a couple of takeaways of course is
知道当然有两点
that scale is everybody's problem not
规模不是每个人的问题
just the big web giant so that's a good
只是大型网络巨头，这是一个很好的选择
thing and a bad thing it doesn't have to
事和坏事，不必
be scary though there are primitives and
尽管有原始元素，但还是要害怕
tools to help make that journey much
工具，以使旅程更加
easier cloud native is after all the new
毕竟，云原生更容易
norm I think you'll agree spring boot is
规范，我认为您会同意 spring boot 是
darn good way to build an API and stand
不错的方法来构建API和站立
that up and get it in production and
将其投入生产
monitored spring cloud simplifies
受监控的弹簧云简化了
integration and interactions between
之间的整合与互动
those api's if you're running this stuff
那些api，如果您正在运行这些东西
that I of course without hesitation
我当然会毫不犹豫地
would recommend a cloud of some sort I
会推荐某种云我
you'll know that I didn't use a cloud
你会知道我没有使用云
here but all of the code and github has
在这里，但所有代码和github都有
a has the appropriate manifest for
具有适当的清单
example to get this running on Cloud
使其在云上运行的示例
Foundry and I'll very shortly have the
铸造厂和我很快就会
appropriate configuration to get it all
适当的配置就可以了
working in a doc arised scenario as well
在出现文档的场景中工作
because it just makes sense this is
因为这很有意义
elasticity you want to build for last
您想要持久建立的弹性
icity and you want to give yourself the
友善，你想给自己
environment that will give you that
环境会给你
elasticity and that is today a cloud
弹性，今天就是乌云
smaller is more less is less is less is
越小越少就是少
bigger and you know always always aim
更大，你知道总是瞄准
for the small thing that can possibly
为了可能的小事
work and as you can see it doesn't have
工作，如您所见，它没有
to be complicated even if you have lots
即使你有很多也要复杂
of little things and in the benefits
小事和好处
outweigh the potential confusion
胜过潜在的混乱
alright thank you very much i'll take
好的，非常感谢，我会接受
some questions now i am as always your
现在有些问题我和你一样
servant if you have questions don't
仆人，如果你有问题不要
hesitate to reach out to me on twitter
犹豫在Twitter上与我联系
at starbucks man that's bx a man or at
在星巴克那是bx一个人或在
my email or spring central of course I
我的电子邮件或Spring Central当然是我
mean we're you know we're all very happy
意思是我们你很开心
to hear from you um the code I've talked
听听你说的我刚才讲的代码
about it on github com for sighs Josh
关于它在github com上让乔什感叹
long and you look for bootiful
很久，你寻找战利品
microservices the spring cloud project
微服务的Spring Cloud项目
is itself a separate organization so get
本身是一个独立的组织，所以请
up comport / spring hype and cloud there
comport /春天的炒作和云在那里
are innumerable many great guides on
有很多关于
spring that I 04 / guides we've just
我04的春天/指导我们刚刚
added in fact a guide on using docker
实际上添加了有关使用docker的指南
with spring-based and spring boot based
基于弹簧和基于弹簧的靴子
applications and another one on using
应用程序和另一个使用
the lattice distributed runtime think of
格子分布式运行时想到的
it more like a coup brunette asaram asos
它更像是一个政变黑发asaram asos
it runs containerized workloads like
它运行容器化的工作负载，例如
docker and that's you know if want to
泊坞窗，这就是您是否要
find out more about that check out
了解有关该签出的更多信息
lattest FCF all right Peter what do you
lattest FCF好的，彼得，你是做什么的
think awesome all right hey did you see
认为还不错吧，你看到了吗
the URL with github com Josh long
带有github com Josh long的URL
beautiful piping hyphen microservice for
美丽的管道连字符微服务
micro services I think it's
我认为这是微服务
microservices great question okay blonde
微服务很棒的问题好吗金发
I'm drug I appreciate that good
我很毒品我很高兴
surrogate and it is microservices okay
代理，可以使用微服务
very good all right cool I just didn't
很好，很好，我只是没有
vote for us conclude that Artem there
投给我们的结论是，阿尔特姆在那里
you go um okay great so we had a bunch
你走吧，好吧，所以我们有一堆
of good questions here um first off is
很好的问题，这里首先是
Ben Zhang asking I've Angeles yeah this
张本问我是安吉利斯吗
was just about 10 minutes ago that he
大约十分钟前
asked this and he says hey if it's the
问这个，他说，嘿，这是
right choice to pass dynamic data
传递动态数据的正确选择
between services such as how many books
服务之间（例如几本书）
are left at my service um if the service
留给我服务吧，如果服务
is service doesn't share the database
是服务不共享数据库
would you know what do you do right in
你知道你在做什么吗
case I mean this is the whole eventual
案例我的意思是这是最终的
consistency thing with microservices
与微服务的一致性
right so you ask the API and is if the
正确，所以您询问API，是
service doesn't pass the data sit again
服务无法通过数据再坐
maybe I misunderstood the question seems
也许我误解了这个问题
a little but so I was I was trying to
有点，但是我当时正试图
paraphrase um because the it's uh it's
释义um因为它是
not straightforward West let me read it
不简单的西方让我读它
literally um if it's right choice to
从字面上看，如果是正确的选择
pass dynamic data between services such
在服务之间传递动态数据，例如
as how many books left in my service
剩下多少本我的服务
if the services don't share the database
如果服务不共享数据库
yea it is definitely that's absolutely
是的，绝对是绝对的
as we pass on information to the API you
当我们将信息传递给您时
want to keep yourself again slight
想再次保持自己的轻微
slight pain in that you have to actually
轻微的痛苦，因为你必须
send the stuff across the wire huge gain
通过电线发送东西巨大的收益
because now your services can be
因为现在您的服务可以
implanted in the choice and then the
植入选择中，然后
best choice for that that betta for the
那个斗鱼的最佳选择
procedure service you know my database
您知道我的数据库的过程服务
selection today may actually be the same
今天的选择实际上可能是相同的
as the selection for another service but
作为另一项服务的选择，但
I may want to move to a different
我可能想搬到另一个地方
database tomorrow and additional I wanna
数据库明天，我想
be able to change my database in my
能够更改我的数据库
schema without having to synchronize on
模式，而不必同步
with everybody else you know so that
与您认识的其他人一起
that that decoupling is very very
那个去耦非常非常
important especially aging move to scale
尤其重要的是老龄化
there's a very of a bounded context did
有一个非常有限的背景
you ever read eric evans amazing domain
您曾经读过eric evans惊人的领域
driven design talks about a bounded
驱动设计谈论有限
context or served services and you know
上下文或提供的服务，您知道
the distribution of responsibilities
责任分配
recommend diving into that for deeper
建议深入研究
discussion ultimate another question
讨论最终另一个问题
from from then when the service is not
从那时起，当服务不
down but off the network the registry
掉线但关闭网络注册表
service will heat wait 1 and mischief i
服务将加热等待1和恶作剧我
can figure out where he started to ask
可以弄清楚他开始问哪里
sorry hang on a second Josh so when the
很抱歉挂在第二个乔希，所以当
service is down but not off the network
服务已关闭但未关闭网络
registry service will something eating
注册服务会吃东西
the service and update the registry
服务并更新注册表
there's a type on here but I'm having
这里有一种类型，但我有
trouble I think what he's kind of
麻烦我想他是什么样的人
getting at is um how is the registry
嗯，注册表如何
kind of service dealing with
与之打交道的服务
unavailability um I think he all right
不可用，我想他没事
so its heart beating human heart beating
所以它的心脏跳动人的心脏跳动
okay so I just figured it out you right
好吧，所以我才知道你是对的
there we go there's a there's a
我们去那里有一个
heartbeat if you have so again the
心跳，如果你又有
service version is ideal for that if you
服务版本是您的理想选择
have network partitions which is going
有要进行的网络分区
to happen right there is a heartbeat
发生就发生心跳
that it goes on between the the clients
它在客户端之间进行
and the the registry and eventually
和注册表，并最终
it'll be decommissioned this is true for
它将退役，这是正确的
all the front of the groove very very
凹槽的前部非常非常
you know important principles of all the
你知道所有的重要原则
different service registries so
不同的服务注册中心
eventually it'll be decommissioned how
最终它将退役
soon it will be
很快它将
Commission is configurable as well in my
我也可以配置佣金
case everything is the default so it's
情况是默认的，所以
about 30 seconds for registration 30
注册30秒约30秒
seconds for heartbeats 30 seconds for
心跳为30秒
whatever but you can find two and all
除了什么，你可以找到两个
that by looking at the properties
通过查看属性
awesome very cool uh let's see um
很棒，很酷，嗯，让我们来看看
Roberto your question what if we use
罗伯托你的问题，如果我们使用
more than one instance because you just
一个以上的实例，因为你只是
add a little more context to that so we
为此添加更多的上下文
know specifically what you're referring
明确知道您指的是什么
to thank you um let's see Stacy Pierce
谢谢你，让我们来看一下Stacy Pierce
asked when you externalized properties
当您外部化属性时询问
it was noted data you had a shared
注意到您共享的数据
application yanil do externalise the
应用程序yanil做外部化
properties for each microservices a
每个微服务的属性a
separate repo or how do you recommend
单独的仓库或您如何推荐
managing so the configuration here in my
管理所以我这里的配置
spring cloud config server which I
我的春季云配置服务器
didn't really mean to dwell on in this
并不是真的想继续讲下去
webinar but thank you for asking it's um
网络研讨会，但感谢您提出要求
it's stood up externally in a single git
它在单个git中从外部站起来
repository each service as identified by
存储由标识的每个服务
their era-appropriate bootstrapped that
他们的时代合适的引导
yeah Mel spring application name loads
是的，Mel spring应用程序名称加载
the configuration from a configuration
配置中的配置
file with that the same name so for
具有相同名称的文件
example my Eureka hyphen service at yamo
例如我在yamo的尤里卡连字符服务
in the git repository is going to only
在git仓库中只会
be read by the service that identifies
由识别以下内容的服务读取
itself as yuri guides and service same
本身作为yuri向导，服务相同
for contacts are the same for bookmark
对于联系人，对于书签而言是相同的
services cetera there's also you know
服务等等，你也知道
this will be loaded and this will be
这将被加载，这将是
loaded with priority but every service
优先，但每项服务
will also get application at yamo
也将在yamo获得申请
application that you mo will be loaded
您将加载的应用程序
first and then specifically based on the
首先，然后专门基于
ID this one will load a second that's
ID这将加载一秒钟的
the spring cloud config server there's
春天的云配置服务器
actually a whole lot of other great
实际上还有很多其他的伟大
stuff you can do with it you can
你可以用它做的事情
actually encrypt passwords for example
例如实际加密密码
and specify a key and the server and
并指定密钥和服务器，以及
then the client to have that decrypted
然后客户端将其解密
in memory and transit and flight as
在记忆中以及过境和飞行中
opposed to storing passwords in plain
反对以简单的方式存储密码
text you can lock down the github
您可以锁定github的文本
repository of course and lock down the
当然，并锁定
config server itself using h2b basic you
配置服务器本身使用H2B基本你
can actually support multiple git
实际上可以支持多个git
repositories now that's actually due to
现在的存储库实际上是由于
a contribution from our pals at a at
来自我们朋友的贡献
ticketmaster in spring cloud can take
春季云的票务主管可以接受
server so I that's all whole other
服务器，所以我就是全部
webinar I I I did a blog on that 12 fact
网络研讨会III在这12个事实上做了一个博客
application style configuration but I I
应用程序样式配置但II
smell the second one coming on I've
闻到第二个来了
already linked to that twice I did it
已经链接了两次，我做到了
early on the beginning of the webinar
网络研讨会开始之初
when you mentioned it and I did it again
当你提到它，我又做了一次
response to this demand another length
对此需求的另一种回应
like two is there Oh make my list you're
就像两个在那儿哦，让我成为你的清单
welcome you're welcome I'm going to skip
欢迎你欢迎我要跳过
over one question because there's one
一个问题，因为有一个
I'd like to see dread like one but I
我想看到像一个恐惧，但我
kind of want to go out of order here and
有点想在这里出故障，
address this one right away 10 Blair
立即解决此问题10布莱尔
asked me what springs up spring is
问我春天是什么春天
sometimes referred to as heavy due to
有时由于
size how does that play in these in
大小如何在这些
these services in particular compared to
这些服务与
juice Jersey etc on netflix open source
netflix开源上的果汁球衣等
oh well I the people that say that I
哦，我那些说我的人
think are I I don't think it's partly
认为我不认为这是部分原因
controversial to suggest that the people
有争议的建议人们
that say that are the people that have
那就是那些拥有
an interest in making spring fail spring
使弹簧失效的兴趣
isn't particularly heavy again each one
每个人都不是特别沉重
of these services is using an embedded
这些服务中使用嵌入式
web server i can use in bed tomcat
我可以在床上使用的Web服务器
embedded jetty whenever that's the same
一样的嵌入式码头
trick as for example something like drop
欺骗，例如掉落之类的东西
wizard is going to do and again embedded
向导将要做，然后再次嵌入
jetty is embedded jelly it weighs so
码头是嵌入果冻，它的重量如此
much you can use Jersey if you want with
如果需要，可以使用很多东西
spring actually we have a here go to
春天实际上我们有一个去
start that spring that I know and you'll
我知道的那个春天开始，你会
see that there's everything's a la carte
看到这里有点菜
right I'm not deploying this to a tomcat
对，我没有将它部署到tomcat
or to a websphere web jboss or whatever
或到websphere网站jboss或其他任何网站
I'm choosing the bits i want nothing
我选择的东西我什么都不想要
more so if i wanted to use jersey i
更重要的是，如果我想使用球衣我
could i don't recommend it again because
我可以不推荐它吗，因为
you're missing out on a lot of the
你错过了很多
features that are full-fledged embassy
完善的使馆特色
in wrists or technology as as you might
尽可能地使用手腕或技术
get from spring MC offers but again
从春季MC获得优惠，但再次
that's there again you don't need
那又是你不需要的
anything but what you need if I want to
除了我需要的东西
just use the just use what the web
只需使用网络即可使用
support and and that's it you know I can
支持，就是这样，您知道我可以
hit a travel 198 great and the web
打一次旅行198很棒，网络
support is going to bring in the
支持将带来
embedded web server that's going to be
嵌入式Web服务器将
tom cat again and I hit generate I want
汤姆猫再次，我打生成我想要
to actually have integration with
真正与
production and the actuator endpoint
生产和执行器终点
that's again that's trivial so I can do
这又是微不足道的，所以我可以做
that there's another one again it
再有一个
becomes very very small because
变得非常非常小，因为
is just pieces it's just the code that
只是片段而已
you need a la carte actually if you look
如果你看的话，实际上你需要点菜
at my jar here that's 22 22.6 Meg's that
在我的罐子里是22 22.6梅格
includes Tomcat in this case you can use
包括Tomcat，在这种情况下，您可以使用
jetty but you'd be yeah I think most
码头，但你会的，我想大多数
people would be surprised to know that
人们会惊讶地知道
Jed is actually a bigger jar footprint
杰德实际上是一个更大的罐子足迹
than in tomcat and you can actually use
比在tomcat中，您可以实际使用
undertow from wild fly from under you
从你下面的野生苍蝇
know for the Red Hat one so this jar if
知道红帽一个，所以这个罐子如果
you recall this is what I looked at when
你还记得这是我什么时候看的
I create a goofy script before again in
我再次创建一个愚蠢的脚本
terms of heavyweight I don't know what
重量级的术语我不知道
that is I don't know how to respond to
那就是我不知道该如何回应
those kind of accusations because you
这类指责是因为你
know if you remember the jar that we
知道你是否还记得我们
created the very beginning it was where
创造了最开始的地方
did I put that right here it was a
我把它放在这里吗
pittance in terms of actual code and
在实际代码方面的重要性和
then the footprint was again it's just
然后足迹再次是
the web server and that's it I mean
网络服务器，就是我的意思
spring missy is just a few hundred
春天小姐只有几百个
kilobytes so that could small as a gift
千字节，所以可以当作礼物
man you just you you can do CF push and
男人，你就是你，你可以做CF推和
push that into the cloud and you're up
将其推送到云中，您就起来了
and running these features don't have to
而运行这些功能则不必
be excessive at all it's only as big as
太过分了
you needed to be and that's the whole
你需要成为，这就是全部
point is you wanted to a couple of stuff
关键是你想要一些东西
right and you just you know you want you
对，你就知道你想要你
need to it helps have something this
需要它帮助有这个东西
modular because your your you know your
模块化，因为您您知道您的
micro service isn't trying to boil the
微服务不是在煮沸
ocean right it should be very tightly
海洋吧，应该非常紧密
scoped all are doing driven design
范围都在做驱动设计
single responsibility principle so your
单一责任原则
list of dependent jars to be you know as
依赖罐子列表
short as you can as short as you can
越短越好
make it and you know at 22 Meg's that's
做到这一点，你知道在22梅格的那是
that's pretty sure to be memory in the
可以肯定的是，
clouds cheap and certainly disk is so
云便宜，当然磁盘是如此
that's that's not particularly um you
那不是你特别
know there must be some other meaning
知道肯定还有其他含义
that i don't know it's either fun or
我不知道这是有趣的还是
there they have some other meeting that
在那里他们还有其他会议
that we're not able to decipher so if
我们无法解密，所以如果
you know what that is can please let us
你知道那是什么可以让我们
know in the meantime on a couple of
同时知道几个
other questions corey asking oh wait
其他问题科里问哦，等等
sorry um I did jump ahead Ben I know you
抱歉，我确实向前走了Ben我认识你
had one or two questions that I haven't
有一个或两个我没有的问题
addressed yet but you've gotten a couple
解决，但你已经得到了一对
in there so I want to let some other
在那儿，我想再放一些
people ask Cory showers asks should we
人们问科里淋浴问我们应该
build microservices by doing synchronous
通过同步来构建微服务
coupling using rest or should we use
耦合使用休息还是我们应该使用
event-based basic between services like
服务之间的基于事件的基础，例如
RabbitMQ or other async methodologies
RabbitMQ或其他异步方法
great question so uh you know who
好问题，所以你知道谁
boy I think you'll see in the next
男孩，我想你会在下一个看到
revision the next sort of major update
修订下一种主要更新
that one of the themes will be bringing
主题之一将带来
in springs amazingly good support for
在春天，对
messaging and integrations it'll be a be
消息传递和集成将是
it through the spring framework proper
通过Spring框架适当
primitives and spring integration for
的原语和spring集成
just that right so yes we of course
就是这样，是的，我们当然
think that messaging is a huge hugely
认为消息传递是巨大的
important way to communicate into to
交流的重要方式
build services but for a lot of people
建立服务，但对很多人来说
rest is just fine it's um a it's it's it
休息就好了，嗯，就是这样
there's a couple places where you're
有几个地方
going to lose time it's if you have a
会浪费时间，如果你有一个
long-running task then you're not going
长期运行的任务，那么你就不会去
to want to use the rest because you're
想用剩下的东西，因为你
going to keep the client block but again
将阻止客户端，但再次
you might be okay with that it's
你可能会同意的
actually the real cost is are you
实际的成本是你
keeping the server blocked and if you're
保持服务器被阻止，如果您
using asynchronous i/o then you're not
使用异步I / O，那么您就不会
you know you're the server is going to
你知道你是服务器要
do background post something whatever it
做背景发布任何东西
does it it's fine and indeed the rest
很好吗，其余的确实吗
request could spawn a message you know
请求可能会产生一条您知道的消息
it could use for example a spring
它可以使用例如弹簧
integration gateway and send off their
集成网关并发送他们的
processing to some back-end grid of
处理到一些后端网格
processing nodes and then get response
处理节点然后获得响应
asynchronously and then send a response
异步然后发送响应
and you say you know using asynchronous
你说你知道使用异步
i/o and you can do that right now in
我/你现在可以在
fact there's a that's easy enough to do
事实上，这很容易做到
just with spring framework and spring
只是与春天的框架和春天
MVC but there is now already support for
MVC，但现在已经支持
if you look and get for spring cloud is
如果你寻找并获得春天的云是
initial cuts on being able to send back
最初的削减能够发回
an observable from our X travel firm
从我们的X旅行社观察到的
spring and Missy a endpoints so again if
春天和小姐的端点如此，如果
you want to run that processing code
您想运行该处理代码
asynchronously and not monopolize
异步而不是独占
threads that's you know that's what a
您知道的线程就是
lot of people are looking for when they
很多人在寻找时
go to messaging messaging
转到消息传递消息传递
does extra it does add another moving
做了额外的事情确实增加了另一个感动
part it adds a broker and the question
部分添加了经纪人和问题
is well what broke are you going to use
很好，你打算用什么破
RabbitMQ is a fine choice I just put a
RabbitMQ是一个不错的选择，我只是放了一个
blog out four days ago or something like
四天前发布博客或类似内容
that on using apache kafka which netflix
关于使用Apache kafka的netflix
use heavily for a lot of their stuff for
大量使用大量东西
something like 300 billion to 800
大约3000亿到800
billion messages per day so again it's
每天有十亿条消息，这又是
there's a lot of different very very
有很多不同非常非常
very cloud scale capable message queues
具有云功能的消息队列
out there and you can tackle some of
在那里，你可以解决一些
those problems now whether it's the best
这些问题现在是否是最好的
choice again it I guess I'm just trying
再选择一次，我想我只是在尝试
to sort of depends on what you're trying
取决于您正在尝试什么
to do if you're trying to get queuing
如果您要排队，该怎么办
and you need to need to have guarantees
而且你需要保证
there then maybe the message queue is
那也许消息队列是
the right way to go if you're just
如果您只是正确的方法
trying to get a synchronous temporally
试图在时间上取得同步
decoupled calls and you can get a lot of
解耦的电话，您可以得到很多
that just from asynchronous i/o which
只是来自异步I / O
you can get today so you know I don't
你今天可以得到，所以你知道我不知道
know so that's that is definitely
知道所以那绝对是
something we're working on that we want
我们想要的东西
to yeah if you have used kisses your
是的，如果您使用过亲吻
spread to your particularly on
传播到你特别
interested in please github right now
现在对github有兴趣
github com pore size spring hyphen cloud
github com孔径春天连字符云
we are mulling the stuff over right now
我们现在正在考虑这些东西
yep this is a big thing excellent um hey
是的，这是一件很棒的大事，嗯，嘿
Ken Kruger how's it going I see a seat
肯·克鲁格（Ken Kruger）近况如何
and Kruger popping up asking him if he
克鲁格弹出来问他是否
could if you could review the dynamic
可以，如果您可以查看动态
port selection there was some code that
端口选择中有一些代码
selected you know dollar Sunport dollar
选择了您知道的美元太阳港美元
said server port 0 oh right so pinky
说服务器端口0哦，好吧，小指
finger thing 0 was like the port
手指的东西0就像端口
randomizer right right so yeah I would
是的，所以我会选择
yeah it's um server that port 0 will
是的，这是um服务器的端口0
randomly select the port that's
随机选择
available what I had was i'm using the
可用的是我正在使用
property placeholder resolution so let
属性占位符解析，所以让
me see bootstrap i know it's an it's in
我看到引导程序，我知道这是一个
here in the application that llamo what
在应用程序llamo这里
I had was doubly nested properly placed
我曾被双重嵌套正确放置
all the resolution so it could be port 0
所有分辨率，因此它可能是端口0
that says if the port variable their use
表示如果端口变量使用
it otherwise you 0 but I also said I
否则你是0但是我也说我
said instead if it's their great
说，如果这是他们的伟大
otherwise another property plays all the
否则，其他财产将发挥所有
revolution if its server
革命，如果它的服务器
Porter their use it otherwise you 0 so
搬运他们使用它，否则你0所以
it's like if this else use this if this
就像这是否其他如果使用
helps you that I'm pretty sure though
可以帮助您，但是我很确定
that can already knew that given that he
既然他已经知道了
knows all the things so did I
知道所有的事情我也是
misunderstand the question can I don't
误会了我的问题
think so um he's probably just 20 out
想想他大概只有20岁
because it might be a little bit of a
因为这可能有点
little bit of a little bit of you know I
一点点的你知道我
said convention over configuration and
所述约定优于配置和
if you don't understand the convention
如果您不了解约定
and then people might have not miss it
然后人们可能不会错过它
um I think maybe he's just trying to
嗯，我想也许他只是想
tell me he didn't think I covered it
告诉我他没想到我覆盖了它
clearly that's a good point yeah I
显然，这是一个好点，是的，我
should have been a little bit more in
应该多一点
detail if I as usual ken love you man
细节，如果我像往常一样肯爱你的男人
send me an email if I can I can do
如果可以的话给我发电子邮件
better all is all is well different all
更好的是所有都是不同的
is well oh by the way he can commented
很好，哦，他可以发表评论
and he felt his opinion was that the
他觉得他的意见是
heavy rate reference refers a bit to jar
重率参考是指罐子
size but also runtime memory consumption
大小以及运行时内存消耗
um yeah nothing to a spring that's you
嗯，没什么是春天
can do terrible things with the
可以用
screwdriver inna place and clout you
螺丝刀inna的地方和影响你
know I think at the end of the day you
知道我想在一天结束时你
know memory this kind of cloud are
知道记忆这种云是
pretty expensive so I mean there's yeah
非常昂贵，所以我的意思是
even that I don't buy the argument I
即使我不赞成我
mean there's no reason it has to be all
意味着没有理由必须全部
of us or all of these services take less
我们或所有这些服务花费更少
than 250 megs of ram all of them
超过250兆公羊
everything I've shown you here so not
我在这里展示给你的一切，所以不是
together I mean each one is less than
我是说每个人都小于
256 megs ram so again and all oh sorry
256兆公羊，所以再次，抱歉
Ruiz ask for a little more explanation
鲁伊斯要求更多解释
on the load balancing bit for spring
在弹簧的负载平衡位上
clouds which is a ribbon I think right
云，这是一条丝带，我认为是正确的
yes sir okay uh what what do you want to
是的，先生，好的，你想要什么
know my friend thumb he was anything
知道我的朋友拇指他是什么
particular he just said for a little hey
特别是他只是说了一点点嘿
just ask for a little more explanation
只是要求更多的解释
you to do me just a quick little review
你给我做一个简短的小回顾
and and comment and move on so ribbon is
然后评论并继续前进，这样功能区是
a configured by spring boot Oh load
一个由 spring boot 配置的哦
balancer auto-configuration Diego
平衡器自动配置Diego
you configure the rest template remember
您配置其余模板请记住
i showed you the the rest of it actually
我给你看了剩下的东西
has the ability to make calls that are
有能力拨打
load balancer and yuiko where that's
负载均衡器和yuiko在那里
actually done right here rest template
实际上在这里完成了休息模板
pop of La Paz in a list of interceptors
拦截器清单中的La Paz流行音乐
right and we're going to inject the load
正确，我们将注入负载
balancer interceptor which is the
平衡器拦截器是
customer that we developed here the load
我们在这里开发的客户负载
balancer interceptor is going to need
平衡器拦截器将需要
the load balancer client the load
负载均衡器客户端负载
balancer interceptors the thing that's
平衡器拦截器是
actually going to call in to live in
实际上要打电话来住
which is the load balancer client object
这是负载均衡器客户端对象
here right and it's going to ask it to
在这里，它将要它
find the appropriate ins for us that bit
找到适合我们的东西
and the ribbon auto configuration you
和功能区自动配置
know this is we actually configure that
知道这是我们实际上在配置
here we configure ribbon load balancer
在这里，我们配置功能区负载平衡器
client and the ribbon load balancer
客户端和功能区负载平衡器
client is where all the magic happens so
客户是所有魔术发生的地方，所以
if you want to override things might
如果您想覆盖事物，则可能
change things this is where you would do
改变这是你会做的事
that here we go choose so what we're
我们在这里选择，所以我们是
saying is
说的是
the server let's see for a service ID
服务器让我们查看服务ID
get load balancer see load balancer to
获取负载均衡器，请参阅负载均衡器
server finally okay so at some point in
服务器终于可以了，所以在某个时候
this chain there's a here we go
这个链子有一个我们要去的地方
in Britain servitor blah blah
在英国，服务员等等
check here
在这里检查
there we go execute I think this is
我们去执行，我认为这是
actual the bit where we drop down so the
实际的位置，我们下降，所以
client factory get load balancer client
客户端工厂获取负载均衡器客户端
get the server open the connection get
获取服务器打开连接获取
requests apply passing in the ribbon
请求申请通过功能区
server so I think that's actually the
服务器，所以我认为这实际上是
yeah that's actually where we get the
是的，这实际上是我们得到的
the the decision on what we want and you
我们想要什么和您的决定
can override what is used right by
可以覆盖使用的权利
specifying your own load balancer I load
指定您自己的负载均衡器
bouncer in this case so they get those
在这种情况下的保镖，所以他们得到那些
bouncer here is going to say hi in fact
保镖实际上会打招呼
to get get load bouncer for this given
得到给定的负载弹跳器
service and then that's going to say get
服务，然后会说得到
instance and then that is going to look
实例，然后看起来
for beans in the context of the type in
用于类型为in的bean
this case the eyelid bouncer so if you
这种情况下眼睑的跳动，所以如果你
configure those it'll it'll use that
配置那些它将使用
otherwise it'll delegate to the conceit
否则会委托自负
this config thing and this is where I
这个配置的东西，这是我在哪里
get a little lost in the code but point
在代码中有点迷失，但要指出
is this is all well documented and it's
这是有据可查的吗？
all happening in the air and what you're
一切都在空中发生，你在做什么
basically trying to do is to configure
基本上要做的就是配置
instances of I load balancer at some
我的负载均衡器实例
point right and that's where is the when
指向右边，那是什么时候
I say I load balancer
我说我的负载均衡器
we are your the the ones that come out
我们是你的那些出来的
of the box there's an abstract one
盒子里有一个抽象的
there's a base one which is you know
有一个基础，你知道
your common dynamics server list bouncer
您的通用动态服务器列表保镖
is the one that we're using in most of
是我们在大多数情况下使用的
the codes by default is the one that
默认情况下，该代码是
takes a collection of service instances
接受服务实例的集合
eventually there's a no-op one that just
最终有一个无人值守的人
does nothing and then there's a think of
什么都不做，然后想到
tanana's on web services zone where load
tanana的网络服务专区
balancer as well you can of course
平衡器当然也可以
implement your own right so you have a
行使自己的权利，以便您拥有
lot of choices here you can easily do
您可以轻松地在这里进行很多选择
the right thing if you want and the
如果您想要正确的事情，
decision is inside arbitrary awesome
决定是在里面很棒
Thank You Josh much appreciated Alvaro
谢谢乔希，非常感谢阿尔瓦罗
hopefully that helps um let's see
希望这可以帮助我们看看
there's a couple more questions that I
我还有两个问题
think we actually might have a shot at
认为我们实际上可能会对
drained me question queue but um let's
耗尽了我的问题队列，但让我们
see pedro el vato asks what are your
看到佩德罗·埃尔·瓦托问你是什么人
recommendations with regarding to
关于的建议
choosing between actually you know what
选择之间，实际上你知道什么
we've heard a little bit about this hold
我们已经听到了一些关于这次举行的消息
on lemme I'm going to park that question
在lemme上，我要提出这个问题
for one more second because there's a
多一秒钟，因为有一个
really good one um where did it go it's
真的很好，嗯，它去了哪里
on security yeah basically I think you
关于安全，是的，基本上我认为你
touched on this a little bit but you
有点感动，但是你
know um you know just basically a
知道，你基本上知道一个
gentleman named broth bharathi was
一位名叫汤·巴拉蒂的绅士
asking how the security services to
询问如何提供安全服务
handle than you we started to touch them
处理得比你，我们开始触摸他们
that a little bit with all tokens and
所有令牌都有一点点
and um you know a lot right right um
嗯，你知道很多吧
yeah so I would encourage you to take a
是的，所以我鼓励您采取
look at spring cloud security which
看一下春云的安全性
builds on top of spring security Oh off
建立在春季安全性之上
spring cloud security makes it simple
Spring Cloud安全性使其变得简单
super super simple to stand up a
超级超级简单站起来
identity provider basically an
身份提供者基本上是
authorization server that if they sign
授权服务器，如果他们签名
off it'll create and serve access tokens
它将创建并提供访问令牌
so it'll set you know you can you can
这样就可以让您知道可以
have an application with an object it'll
有一个带有对象的应用程序
be it'll have a challenge authentication
它将具有挑战身份验证
challenge the application challenge will
挑战应用挑战
be forwarded to the identity provider
被转发给身份提供者
like like the authorization server that
就像授权服务器一样
serves authorization tokens and if it's
提供授权令牌，如果有的话
valid it'll the authorization server
有效它将授权服务器
will give
会给
I would an access token and then all of
我要一个访问令牌，然后所有
the different microservices can point to
不同的微服务可以指向
that authorization server and say you
那个授权服务器说你
know now you need to get malposition
知道现在你需要错位
server from this service and they'll
服务器从此服务，他们将
know to automatically redirect to that
知道自动重定向到那个
authorization server if there's an
授权服务器（如果有）
invalid request without Nexus token in
没有Nexus令牌的无效请求
the body again you can use spring cloud
身体再次可以用春云
securities o ox based off identity
基于身份的证券
server or you can just point to you know
服务器，或者您可以指向您知道
Facebook or github or whatever you can
Facebook或github或任何您可以
use you can use somebody else's
用你可以用别人的
alongside the identity server but the
身份服务器旁边，但是
result is that you have a suite of
结果是您有一套
services with one annotation and a few
一个注释和几个注释的服务
config properties basically telling it
配置属性基本上可以说明这一点
where to look for the endpoint that can
在哪里寻找可以
be used to decrypt an access token and
用于解密访问令牌和
that's it in a lot of XP you know in
在您知道的许多XP中就是这样
every protected resource will
每个受保护的资源将
automatically know to call this
自动知道叫这个
authorization provided as identity
授权作为身份提供
provider and go through the flow of
提供者，并经历
getting an access token if you want to
如果要获取访问令牌
learn like a lot more i cannot i cannot
学到更多，我不能，我不能
more emphatically recommend it but you
更强调地推荐它，但是你
want to learn a lot about this stuff
想学到很多东西
don't hesitate to check out the good
不要犹豫，检查好
doctor Dave sires amazing 7 part now
医生戴夫（Dave）先生现在令人惊叹的7部分
blog series on single page apps with
单页应用程序上的博客系列
angularjs and spring security and spring
angularjs和spring安全性和spring
cloud zool and spring cloud security and
云动物和春季云安全和
spring session and just just awesome
春天的会议，真是太棒了
yeah you started back in December and
是的，您从十二月份开始
it's just it's been phenomenal so if you
只是它非常了不起所以如果你
want to learn about that this is it's a
想知道这是一个
great way to go and he talks about
好方法，他谈论
spring cloud security yep there's a lot
春天云安全是很多
in there that's great thank you very
在那里，非常感谢
much um awesome okay so Pedro a couple
非常好，所以佩德罗夫妇
more questions and I think we're going
还有更多问题，我想我们要去
to cut it at the half hour here on Jorge
在半小时的时间里将其削减到豪尔赫
Lee asks how easy is it to override
李问覆盖有多容易
those yellow configurations for
那些黄色的配置
automated testing very uh so again if
自动化测试非常呃，如果
you saw in the in the beginning when I
你在一开始就看到
could at GUI application I specified on
可以在我指定的GUI应用程序上
the command line here I'm sorry and he
命令行在这里，很抱歉，他
goes on to ask just just so you hit the
继续问只是让你打
shape because it's just you hit the same
形状，因为只是你打相同
topic same time he's also curious like
同时他也很好奇
how do you swap the config based on
你如何交换基于的配置
profile or environment settings you know
您知道的配置文件或环境设置
this is kind of
这是一种
just going with this all right so it's
就这样就可以了
what I override individual little
我超越个人的一点点
properties again you can do for example
再次可以做一些属性
Java minus D server that port equals
Java减去D服务器的端口等于
eight thousand minus star whatever right
八千颗负星无论如何
battle or high that jar like that you
战斗或高个像你这样的罐子
can do things like that so that'll be
可以做那样的事情，这样
dash the arguments or we can say export
破折号或我们可以说出口
server underscore port equals nine
服务器下划线端口等于9
thousand and then do double my star
千，然后把我的星星加倍
that's that's certain going to work as
那肯定会像
well but whoa okay but you can also if
好吧，但是哇，但是你也可以
are as profiles are going to concerned
就像个人资料要关注的一样
in your config server store for example
例如在您的配置服务器存储中
bookmark heights and service hyphen
书签高度和服务连字符
cloud or dev or whatever and that will
云或开发人员或其他任何东西
be loaded based on the profile is active
根据配置文件被激活
when the request is when they when the
当请求是什么时候，当他们
application starts up so it'll load the
应用程序启动，因此它将加载
right configuration file based on the
正确的配置文件基于
profile in the running client
正在运行的客户端中的配置文件
application so I think that's probably
应用程序，所以我认为这可能是
what you're looking for perfect um let's
您正在寻找完美的东西，让我们
see whether recommendations on whether
看看是否有建议
your recommendations with regards to you
关于您的建议
again we heard this in the last webinar
我们在上次网络研讨会上再次听到了
Josh right what are your recommendations
乔希，对您有什么建议
with regards are choosing an
考虑到选择
implementation for service registry no
服务注册表的实现否
console zookeeper Eureka on say if
控制台动物园管理员尤里卡（Eureka）说
you're just getting started with service
您才刚开始使用服务
discovery as such I I would start with
这样的发现将始于
Eureka it's darn good it certainly works
尤里卡真是太好了，它当然有效
at scale it's being used by Netflix them
Netflix正在大规模使用它们
it's easy enough to stand up as you can
站起来很容易
see it's just an annotation and a
看到它只是一个注释和一个
dependency import away from working so I
依赖导入无法正常工作，所以我
would start with that that is it's
从那开始就是
definitely the most friendly to get
绝对是最友好的
started with console is by the same
从控制台开始是相同的
folks who built the surf and vagrants on
在海浪上游荡的人们
and had some really really smart
并有一些非常聪明的人
features it's written in go so it
它是用go编写的功能
doesn't pose a slight bit more
一点也不构成
deployment complexity but again I don't
部署的复杂性，但我又没有
think that's really a problem for most
认为这对大多数人来说确实是一个问题
modern teams
现代团队
it has some really really cool features
它有一些非常酷的功能
so again that's worth checking out but
所以再次值得一看，但是
if you're looking for just a straight
如果您正在寻找一条直线
straight up very very simple service
直接非常非常简单的服务
registry tard to beat Eureka zookeeper
登记处击败尤里卡动物园管理员
can do uh it's actually using it as a
可以做到，实际上是将其用作
service registry in the same way that we
服务注册中心的方式与我们
might use a Eureka is a disservice to do
可能使用尤里卡是无益的
keeper zookeepers actually capable a lot
饲养员实际上有能力
more right it actually has a its niche
更正确的是，它实际上有其利基
is coordination information so you can
是协调信息，因此您可以
for example handle a very very weird
例如处理一个非常非常奇怪的
special as I specialized topologies and
特殊的，因为我专门拓扑
hand up for example situations where
例如举手
forgettable unknown may go down and you
难忘的未知可能会消失，你
want to know you eat you don't want to
想知道你吃东西，你不想
have the split plane problem and you
有分裂飞机的问题，你
want to make sure that if a service is
想确保是否有一项服务
the master then you know it's either you
主人那么你知道是你
evict it from the cluster quickly or
迅速将其从集群中逐出或
whatever you have a very very a lot of
不管你有很多
power there you know and it can
你知道那里的力量，它可以
detection a set of low level primitives
检测一组低级原语
so while spring cloud can treat it and
因此，尽管春云可以治疗它，
use it as a as a low-level services
用作低层服务
train just fine it actually have a lot
训练得很好，实际上有很多
more power that one I would say is the I
我会说的是我更多的力量
would tackle that one if you're not
如果你不解决的话
entirely satisfied with the other ones
对其他人完全满意
first that one's really really powerful
首先，一个人真的很强大
it certainly works as well it's at scale
它当然也可以正常运行
I mean we we use it in spring XD Apache
我的意思是我们在Spring XD Apache中使用它
Kafka uses it you know we have a
卡夫卡使用它，你知道我们有一个
preliminary support not just for using
初步支持不仅仅用于
as uzuki as a discovery engine but as a
作为uzuki作为发现引擎，但作为
service broker but as also as a a
服务经纪人，但也一样
framework for dynamically electing
动态选举的框架
certain nodes as leader for example a
某些节点作为领导者，例如a
certain bowls you can say okay well if
某些碗，如果你可以说很好
this if my node gets it gets elected as
这如果我的节点得到它被选为
a leader promised an application event
一位领导答应了申请活动
for example so there's a lot of really
例如，有很多真正的
powerful things you can do there and
您可以在那里做的强大的事情，
that's actually code that and get out
那实际上是编码并离开
right now that you can poke around it
现在你可以在它周围戳
and if you have use cases were always
如果有用例，总是
very keen on hearing those as well
也非常喜欢听那些
that's that's certainly one of the
那肯定是其中之一
things we're focusing on the more
我们正在关注的事情更多
complex interactions there
那里复杂的互动
alright this stuff there and of course
好吧，那里的东西，当然
you may not need a service fee if you're
如果您是，则可能不需要服务费
running inside of a lattice for example
例如在晶格内运行
you can use the sprinkler spring cloud-
您可以使用洒水弹簧云-
project and that will give you a
项目，这会给你一个
discovery client implementation that is
发现客户端实现
that will use it because again mattis
会用它，因为再次是螳螂
knows which API which which node is
知道哪个节点是哪个节点
running which application and that is to
运行哪个应用程序
say which service so you can you can ask
说出哪种服务，以便您可以询问
it in the same way you could Eureka you
就像你可以用尤里卡一样
know for this service ID give me the
知道这个服务ID给我
host imports and depending for springing
主机进口，取决于反弹
cloud and cloud foundry that supported
云和支持的云代工厂
on the way to so you know maybe you
在去的路上，所以你知道也许你
don't need it you know or maybe and
你不需要它，也许或者
there's no reason you couldn't use for
没有理由你不能使用
example we go on top of class under
例如我们在课堂上
indeed we're actually standing up push
确实，我们实际上是站起来
button deployment of eureka on top of
在顶部放置尤里卡按钮
credit but again maybe you just want
信用，但也许你只是想
that that mapping and that's already
那个映射已经是
maintained by the platform okay whoo all
由平台维护好所有
right so the questions are continuing to
对，所以问题继续
come in but i think we're going to have
进来，但我认为我们将有
to call it it's were 30 minutes after
叫做30分钟后
and we usually we usually really try not
而且我们通常通常真的不尝试
to go any longer than that and we're
再走下去，我们
only we're down to only 100 people now
现在只有100人
where we had a a couple hundred before
我们之前有几百个
so I think we're think we're pretty much
所以我认为我们认为我们非常
at time I'm great to hear from you tube
当时我很高兴收到你的来信
and Kruger yep um and yes so just to let
和克鲁格是的，是的，所以让
a quick bit of housekeeping we are
我们快速整理房间
recording this and it will be posted
记录下来，它将被发布
right to spring down iof / / video again
再次弹出iof //视频的权利
spring that I oh /video yes we always
春天，我哦/ video是的，我们永远
record you know Josh posis slides up to
记录一下，您知道Josh posis滑到
a speaker deck and then the slide link
扬声器座，然后滑动链接
will be in the the blog post so again if
将在博客文章中，因此再次
you want to get a notification on when
您想获得有关何时的通知
this is with replays available just
这是重播功能
going to spring that I Oh forward slash
即将到来的春天，我哦，正斜线
blog and subscribe there to the atom
博客并在那里订阅原子
feed that's a--that's a great way
喂-这是一个好方法
because when we post the replay we
因为当我们发布重播时，
always make a blog post on that embed
总是在该嵌入上发表博客文章
the YouTube video and that'll have all
YouTube视频，然后将所有内容
the information you looking for I'm
您正在寻找的信息是
sorry my machine is kind of freaking out
对不起，我的机器有点吓坏了
so I'm missing a little information
所以我缺少一些信息
hang on one second yep anytime um on
随时挂一秒钟
April twenty-eighth come back atcha if
如果四月二十八号回来
you're interested at all in Apache Kafka
您对Apache Kafka完全感兴趣
and high-speed messaging but type stuff
和高速消息传递，但输入内容
like poor it like that gentleman Cory
像那位先生科里一样可怜
was you should come back on April
你应该在四月回来吗
twenty-eighth the Springsteen team's
Springsteen团队的第二十八名
gonna be talking about a patchy caca um
会谈论一片斑驳的可卡姆
and doing reactive data pipelines with
并与
spring XD and an Apache kafka so I think
Spring XD和Apache Kafka，所以我认为
it was the quarry you might might be
这可能是采石场
really interested in that one I'm going
我对那个我真的很感兴趣
to attempt to post the vlog here hang on
尝试在这里发布视频博客
some I just kind of lost the chat window
一些我只是失去了聊天窗口
hold on one second folks see there we go
抱一秒钟的人看到我们去了
I hope that works josh did you just full
我希望乔希的作品能使您吃饱
screen yep okay all right that's okay
屏幕是，好吧，好吧
got it missing oh cool yeah of course is
丢失了哦，很酷，是的，
excellent thanks okay um Cory yeah it's
很好，谢谢，嗯，Cory是的
don't miss it webinar by the way folks
大家不要错过网络研讨会
Mario smoker machine dr. Pollock that's
马里奥吸烟机博士波洛克
awesome sure the formatting is coming
很棒，确定格式即将到来
through all weird hopefully that's
通过所有奇怪的希望是
enough for you to get it Cory sorry
足以让你得到它
about that let me try one last time with
关于这一点，让我最后一次尝试
this URL the formatting guy kind of
这个网址是格式化人员
introduce some line breaks there and got
在那儿引入一些换行符
messed up let's see if that works oh
搞砸了，让我们看看是否可行哦
come on yeah it just doesn't start the
来吧是的，它只是没有开始
line breaks its introducing are not
换行符不是
going to make it cut and copyable but
将其剪切并复制，但
yeah great thanks Cory you got it
是的，非常感谢Cory，你明白了
awesome on so by the way if you want to
太棒了，顺便说一句，如果你想
get your hands on dips um just make a
让您沾沾上嗯，只是做一个
note that we don't really encourage you
请注意，我们并不是真的鼓励您
to direct download spring bits by HTT
通过HTT直接下载弹簧钻头
HTT P direct we really want to encourage
HTT P direct我们真的很想鼓励
you to use maven cradle as it's just
您可以使用Maven通讯座
better if however you're you know just
更好，但是如果你知道
you're stuck behind knowing learners or
您被困在了解学习者的背后或
proxy servers or you work on a military
代理服务器或您在军队中工作
network or close government network or
网络或紧密的政府网络或
something like that um you can get HTTP
像这样的东西，你可以得到HTTP
downloads we just don't make it super
下载，只是我们不让它变得超级
easy to be honest um and those are
坦率地说，嗯，这些是
available at repo spring i oh if for
可在repo spring上购买
some reason you need a direct HTTP
由于某些原因，您需要直接使用HTTP
download really encourage you to use
下载确实鼓励您使用
maven or if you know encourage your
专家或如果您知道鼓励您
organization best
最好的组织
best case to set up a private naman on
在上面建立私人纳曼的最佳案例
your network so that you can use it on
您的网络，以便您可以在
and let us know your feedback on the the
让我们知道您对
spring cloud team would love to hear
春云团队很想听听
from you if you want you can you can
从你那里，如果你愿意，你可以
tweet any of your feedback back to them
将您的任何反馈转发给他们
at a spring cloud OSS and it's right
在春季云OSS上，是正确的
there on the right end the chat um and
在右边的聊天室，
yeah um like I said there will be a blog
是的，就像我说过会有博客
post spring I 04 / video with the replay
发布春季I 04 /视频重播
and the slides so again let's hear it
和幻灯片，让我们再次听到
for for Josh long for incredibly
对于Josh来说，真是令人难以置信
detailed awesome presentation on a
详细的精彩演讲
really difficult topic in distributed
分布式中非常困难的话题
computing that you know we're working
计算您知道我们正在工作
hard to make easier for you guys so I'm
很难让你们更容易，所以我
Josh thanks a lot I learned a lot from
乔希非常感谢，我从中学到了很多
this presentation is good too anything
这个演讲太好了
you want to say before we close it out
你想在我们结束之前说
and call it a day no thank you guys see
并称之为一天，不，谢谢大家看到
you online all right oh yeah take care
你在线上，好吧，哦，保重
everyone appreciate your time any
每个人都感谢你的时间
questions look forward to seeing you on
问题期待着您的光临
april 20 for the coffee or water take
4月20日拿咖啡或水
care yeah that'll be great don't miss it
呵呵，那会很棒的，不要错过
you
您